Mr. President.
It's the president. He's hot.
So?
Nothing for now.
No news?
Mmmm.
All right, so, uh, his condition is stable.
But I can't promise anything.
You should expect the worst. What?
Is my husband going to be disabled?
No, no, no. That's not possible.
He's not going to, okay? I've cleaned old white people's poop here.
I've cleaned their pee. Never again.
Can you see me taking care of a vegetable like this…
No, no, no, no, no. I'd rather him be dead.
Well, in that case, that's good, because his life might be cut short.
Is it okay that I see him?
Of course, Mr. President.
Dad.
It's Stéphane, your son.
I know we don't know each other well…
but I was really hoping we could make up for lost time, Dad.
Sensation.
What?
Dad, what? What's happening? Are you feeling your hand, your legs?
Pleasure.
It makes me pleased to know that you're still alive, Dad.
Anus.
Did he speak?
Uh, yeah, I think his subconscious mind is speaking.
REPRESENT
Yesterday, Claude Blé, the president's father,
was the victim of a horrifying attack.
He's currently in a deep coma.
How is the president? He's deeply affected, obviously,
but he's safe right now,
and intends to run his campaign for the legislative elections.
The Élysée would also like to thank and acknowledge
the efficiency of the police,
who arrested the alleged offender.
He's being held in the antiterrorist unit as we speak.
What about the Queen of Norway's visit? Is it cancelled?
No, it's not. Uh, in spite of the events,
the president will still meet with Queen Anne of Norway.
Per Mrs. Douanier's wishes, he'll be inflexible on ecology,
whale hunting, and oil exploitation in the North Sea.
Any other questions?
Besides "Why wear a hijab
while Iranian women fight for their right to take it off?"
Yeah. That's what I thought.
Thanks.
Mr. President, I just wanted to say,
I know I wasn't on my game in regard to what took place,
but I can assure you that you are now completely safe at the Élysée.
Sorry, excuse me? I just wanted to discuss with you…
What? But it's about time, isn't it?
After two assassination attempts. Thanks for the favor.
Okay Honestly, thanks a lot.
Yeah, all right Can we say "thanks"?
Thanks, you're welcome. But security isn't an exact science.
It should be. I just wanted to say,
don't go meet the suspect.
We know it's him who helped the other terrorist, and you're safe now.
Mo agrees with me. I want to know what's on his mind.
Come on. It's Can I talk with him?
No, it's a bad idea. Why do you want to?
We perfectly know what's in his mind. He's a disgusting white fascist…
Well, no. …who eats sauerkraut.
Mr. President, it's not what you think. Let's go.
No. Yes, okay, let's go. As you wish.
Anyway, you decide.
Filthy Negro.
Huh?
Did I just hear an accent? Jesus Christ!
It's him?
Yeah, yeah, I mean, I warned you. Yes, it's me.
And I have no regrets.
I'd do it again, if I could. If given the chance, I wouldn't hesitate.
My brother, wait, what's your problem? I don't understand.
Who's your brother, you baboon? Huh? You're not my president.
People like you want to steal all the baguettes from the French.
And you take advantage of state benefits.
Wait, I… Ahem.
People like him are people like you. What do you mean?
You, hijab girl.
Don't you have a sheep to butcher in your bathtub?
Do you find that funny? Not at all.
No, I'm not laughing, but it was kind of funny.
Shut your mouth, you Turk.
Think I'm a Turk, man?
Come on, I'll show you… No.
Me, Turkish? Bitch. What the fuck? Stop.
I've got Black features. My father is Black, all right?
Calm down. Chill now, William. Hey, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on. Hold on.
My brother, I don't…
I don't know what's going on.
Maybe you just got your citizenship, so you're feeling emotional,
but you're losing it, my friend.
I'm on your side, man. You're someone's pawn.
Really? On my side? On my side to give me what?
What are you going to do for me that French people haven't already done for me?
I'm a French citizen. From Chambéry.
What we want right now is to send you back to your jungle of monkeys.
There.
We want a real president. A French president of France.
What did he say?  I spoke Creole.
Yeah, right. Sometimes you add some R's and sometimes you remove them, hmm?
I mean, he thinks he's more Creole than red beans and rice.
He might as well learn the language.
While some mandates start with a state of grace,
that of President Blé is already a fiasco.
Following the assassination attempt on his father,
Stéphane Blé will attempt to regain his composure
by hosting the Queen of Norway with grandeur and formality.
However, this visit has already sparked controversy,
with critics expressing their concerns about excessive spending
during a time of economic hardship for the French people.
As the legislative elections approach,
President Blé appears to be in a precarious situation,
confined within the walls of the Élysée.
Cognard for president!
Cognard for president! Thank you. Thank you.
First and foremost, I would like to wish a speedy recovery
to Mr. Claude Blé.
He's faking it!
No, it's all good. It's all good.
We know that he's from the Ivory Coast.
So he'll get free treatment.
Thanks a lot, France.
I am here with you today because we have had enough.
Exactly.
Hey, Blé!
We're fucking starving, Blé!
WE BEHEADED LOUIS XVI WE CAN DO IT AGAIN
His "living together" ideals and his "France mleh,"
that's just hot air.
It's a scam!
He's playing with us while stuffing our money in his pockets.
That's right!
We don't have a president anymore, but an African king.
Legislative elections are a long way off. We want power, and we want it now.
Yeah!
GET OUT, BLÉ
Blé, resign now! Blé, resign now!
Blé, resign now!
Am I interrupting?
No, no, come in.
Blé, resign now!
You're not our president!
Are you okay?
Soso. Everyone hates me.
Unless there's a miracle, I'm gonna get crushed at the legislative elections.
No, it's…
I was supposed to go to Guadeloupe for the béké tax, but…
I think I'll stay.
No, actually, you should go to Guadeloupe. It's important.
Are you sure? Be careful over there.
People are really angry. Yeah.
Really. Ask your guy to come with you.
Aimé? Yeah.
I'm not sure if that's necessary.
Yeah, it's important. But he can't leave you alone.
I'll make sure to ask Mo to keep me in the loop.
Okay.
Not everyone hates you, Stéphane.
I don't hate you.
Hey, what are you doing?
May I kiss you?
Of course not.
I respect that.
I should hope that you respect that, Stéphane.
What if I insist a bit? It's called marital rape.
Even if you're my wife? Especially because I'm your wife.
That's the concept. Hence, marital. Hmm. Mmhmm.
We're not like that.
No, not like that at all. It's haram, yeah.
Worse.
Heard of hell? Mm.
Touch me again and I send you there on a bobsled, okay?
Alhamdullilah. Loud and clear. Got it?
All right. We'll be in touch. Let's keep in touch.
See you later, baby.
What did you say?
Let's see each other after the béké thing. The béké tax, béké family…
Uhhuh.
Don't let the demonstrations get to you.
First of all, there are only men, and on top of it,
it's obviously led by the far right.
What do you think? I deal with that every day at Matignon.
"Lesbian," "feminazi," "tree hugger," so…
Why bother, you know? I can't help but bother, honestly.
Every night, I hear, "Blé, you're a dead man!"
"Blé, your mother drinks Sprite!"
Guess what I else heard? "Blé, your mom's in a boubou thong."
I googled it. They don't even exist. Boubou thong.
Come on, forget about it.
It's the old confusion between tradition and eroticism.
It's exhausting.
Okay, so…
I know why you're inviting the Queen of Norway.
Hold on, let me explain.
Come on, Corinne It's a symbol.
And it's powerful, like those from the bottom facing those from the top.
A multicultural nation like France facing the old Europe.
It's so powerful.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
That's exactly it.
Wow!
But I'll give you my notes on the fishing quotas,
the slaughter of the whales, offshore gas, fossil fuel.
Yeah, I'd love to, I'd love to. Not "I'd love to." You have to work.
Stéphane, it's super important. Mmhmm.
If you make the Queen of Norway give in, your mandate is assured.
You'll be the king of the world. Mmhmm.
However, if you mess it up…
you'll disappoint millions of us.
And you'll end up in the trash cans of history.
Blue trash can or black trash can?
No. I never joke about recycling.
Me either.
A piece of paper in the sewers, know where it ends up?
The sewers?
On a turtle's head, fool.
Don't make any concessions with the queen.
PRESIDENT BLÉ WELCOMES QUEEN OF NORWAY
You have to sell some fighter jets, or we're screwed.
Uh, I'm not sure Corinne will agree to that.
Corinne doesn't decide. Neither do you, okay?
Right now, the Norwegians have us by the balls.
They decide.
Do you know why this whole ambassador story hasn't been leaked yet?
They want to use it for leverage. To better negotiate.
We can't do anything.
If that gets out, you and Mo are out.
Like far out. You too?
Not at all. You have to be a good negotiator with the queen.
How good are you? Me?
So, one time, I went to the market in Marrakesh
Yeah, all right, you suck. We gotta find something else.
She's old, you're young.
You don't have, uh, a goodlooking face.
But in there, there must be something.
What are you talking about?
Come on, spit.
Stop it.
That's what she wants.
You nuts? Cut it out. That's not my thing.
Oh, it's not your thing? No, it's Mo's thing, but it's not for me.
Of course, it's everyone's thing. That chick is pretty hot.
Check her out. Are you saying it's your thing?
Huh?
No.
No, but uh…
she's not ugly.
I could do it, I could do it. Stop.
I won't do that.
All right, then we have to find something else.
You should look pitiful.
Do your typical dumb African look.
A classic.
There, that one. It's great.
What? I did nothing. You did.
You had your eyes like this, looking completely lost.
Like an African guy saying, "Hey, what's happening right now?"
It was great. What were you thinking about? Nothing?
Well, then do that.
Keep that.
All right? Let's do that.
In front of the queen, you go,
"Oh, really? I ain't got no idea on the matter." Okay?
The door!
It's not in my job to do that. Guys, it's not my job…
You okay? Yeah, I'm fine.
Relax, relax.
What did you put on? What's that?
It's Norwegian, to win her favor.
I've never seen a Norwegian rocking this awful thing, dude.
Come on, it's their custom. Take it off, take it off.
Her Majesty, the Queen Anne of Norway.
Your Highness, this way!
Please, Your Highness!  To the left!
Your dress is beautiful.
What made you want to come and visit him?
Kiss her. Kiss her. Huh?
Kiss her hand. Oh.
Too noisy. Way too noisy.
Welcome to France, Your Majesty.
Thank you for your hospitality!
Her Royal Highness thanks you for your hospitality.
That's what I thought.
All right.
Welcome.
Bambambambam.
Cut it out. Sorry.
Let me introduce you to Djigui.
Hello. He's one of the best entrepreneurs here.
A remarkable success story of going from rags to riches.
Nice to meet you. He's an event planner.
Did you rent your tuxedo?
I'd also like to introduce you to Lamine.
I love him like a son. A very talented and good chef.
He's been cooking for a year.
Good day.
It's a pleasure. He's so cute.
Hello.
Stéphane isn't a good person. He's a loser.
Shh! Uh, my friend, you don't need to translate that.
It's all good, okay? Jeanette!
This is my mother, Simone.
Nice to meet you, Your Highness.
My mother is religious, as you are.
Do you go to church every Sunday like we do?
To the temple. Her Royal Highness is a protestant.
Protestants are often liars.  All right then.
All right, let's cut to the chase.
We're going to sit down for the rest of the protocol, please.
Jeanette, why are you doing this? Well, simply because I don't like to lie.
You're annoying.
It's all good. Marion's arrived safely in Guadeloupe.
Zero problem. She's at the Blue Parrot Hotel.
Cool. Is that a nice hotel?
Yeah, um, it's nice. Very nice.
Very nice.
"Near the most beautiful beaches of the island,
the Blue Parrot Hotel is a lovers' paradise."
"In the shade of the palm trees,
you'll be able to fulfill your wildest fantasies."
That's a nice description.
Yeah.  I'm glad she's in a nice spot.
Yeah, it's cool. Goes to show the gays have good taste.
Keep me posted.
Yeah, I'll keep you posted, brother.
Oh fuck. Fuck.
I have a question. Huh?
What's with that guy giving you the stink eye?
Who's giving me the stink eye? Over there.
Where? Where?
Oh.
Um, racism.
There's a lot of racism in Norway. I mean, it's real.
Good evening to all of you.
Uh, in honor of the esteemed visit from the Queen of Norway,
I have made the choice to introduce a traditional "ailing" dancer.
"Halling. Halling."
Right. Halling.
No, it's not Arabic. It's Norwegian.
Halling!  Yeah.
It's not easy to say.
Whoo!
Whoa.
He's really good with his leg.
He's really flexible. Pretty good.
Bravo.
Fantastic.
Bravo.  She congratulates you.
Am I not treating you like a king or something?
Right? This whole ambassador thing, can't we solve it together, or no?
I would very much like to see you dance halling.
The Queen would like to see you dance a halling.
What?
Halling.
Right now.
Go ahead.
Uh, you want me to dance now?
Mm.
Hold on.
What's up?
She wants me to dance a halling now.
Ah, fuck.
Well, listen, uh, that's some weird old Norwegian chick's kink, you know?
Yeah, but what do I do? Well, you do it. What else?
No! Well, you're her bitch, man.
So either you do what she tells you to do, or you end up in prison.
So go halling. Go do it.
Come on. Halling. Halling for the president.
Halling! Halling! Halling!
For Norway!
You're the bitch of Norway. Come on. It was planned, y'all.
It was planned all along.
Of course it was planned.  Yeah, of course.
Come on.
Cool.
Three, four.
Superb.
Awesome. Honestly, he's pretty good.
Wow.
Loser.
He can't even dance.
The white man danced better than him.
Bravo!
Wow, wow!
The Queen congratulates you.
So, are we even now?
Is it cool? We even?
Listen, little shit.
Listen carefully, little shit.
She really said "little shit" to me, or…  She did, yes.
Don't give a fuck about halling.
I don't give a fuck about halling.
If I tell the press you beat up my ambassador…
If we tell the media that you beat up my ambassador…
…your buddy gets life in jail.
…your bud gets life in prison.
You'll be charged with aiding.
You go down for aiding.
So it is in your interest to be generous.
So you'd better be very generous, biatch.
"Biatch," did you come up with that, or was that her?
I added that part. Oh.
So what have you got for us?
Well, I've…
I've thought about it, and I'm thinking…
Three Rafale jet fighters should be enough.
And we call it even.
Would three Rafale fighter jets be enough?
Three Rafales? Yeah.
Three Rafales?
All right, five. But I won't offer any more than that.
Five Rafales, game over. That's all. Deal. Case closed.
Five is the best he can do.
But he's a complete idiot.
Mm.
I thought we'd be negotiating…
Five.
…one or two North Sea fishing quotas.
Are we in business?
Ask him for a nuclear power plant.
Your Majesty, he can't be that stupid.
Just ask him.
The five Rafale fighters aren't enough.
We want a nuclear plant too.
She's really good.
She's quite the business whiz.
But that's a no. I have to say no.
No. I won't budge.
And you can look at me with your beautiful blue eyes
and your beautiful interpreter blue eyes,
and your blond hair that's soft like silk, I won't budge.
I just won't. Sorry.
You can even tell her in her language.
That means absolutely nothing.
And it's racist.
That's true.
I apologize. It was stupid. Really sorry.
Forgive me?
All right. You rock.
["Nubian Farlow" by Varnish La Piscine playing]
Aren't you ashamed of yourself? What's going on?
Why did you do that?
Why did you sell Rafale fighters and nuclear plants to Norway?
Uh, it's not all what you think. Let me explain.
I thought we agreed.
How could you betray me like this? How could you betray us all like this?
Betray France?
I was inflexible about the whales. Yeah, great.
They won't be killed by harpoons, but exterminated by radioactive waste.
Awesome. Believe me, I couldn't do anything.
You could have chosen.
You know that I support all your causes, everything.
In fact, we're gonna do something for Tibet soon.
I don't follow.
Well, your hat and all that.
Not at all, I just find it beautiful.
Oh. And don't change the subject.
Why did you sell Rafale fighters and nuclear plants to Norway?
What did I tell you?
It's top secret.
So you're a liar on top of being a coward. You really are a man. You know what?
"Your words are like a bizarre melody
Deception dances upon your tongue
A web of lies are spun
These lights so dim won't light your path
Leaving you in gloom
No matter how you try
They won't shine bright Like stars in the sky on a dark night
For the one who comes one day A fleeting stay
Like a whisper in the wind Slipping into the void"
Here. What is that?
What is it? Read it.
What's this thing?
I can't read it.
It's smeared.
Can you see?
No, I can't read it.
Oh, it's because ink without additives.
On recycled paper, it smears.
You have to use one or the other, but both together, it doesn't work.
Anyway, it's my resignation. Hold on.
Stop playing with me. No, I'm not.
You know what? You used to be a good person.
But now, you're a piece of shit. Politics turned you.
And I won't become a piece of shit. So I'm leaving, goodbye, I quit.
Long live the republic.
Fuck, I'm sure she's radicalized.
I'll put her on the terrorist watch list.
We know white women like this.
First they speak Arabic, then they bomb the Métro.
With us tonight, Madam Prime Minister.
Let's talk about your resignation.
Why do you think French people don't trust politics anymore?
Why are they angry? Because they've been betrayed.
They've been lied to.
As a matter of fact, President Blé got elected on a social platform,
and as soon as he's in power, he sells weapons and nuclear plants.
He shouldn't be surprised by the disavowal of the people.
If he wants to behave like an asshole, that's his choice.
But I won't follow his path. Neither will the French.
I really don't want to go, to be completely honest.
Do you think I want to go?
Let me remind you we don't have a political party.
He's got a structure, local supporters.
With him, we have a chance to win.
But without him, the far right will be in charge in a month.
Guaranteed.
With Cognard in Matignon, we'll deal with deportations.
It'll be horrible.
No more France Blé. It's France mleh.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Honestly, I don't want to do it. You do. You're staying.
Come on, Stéphane, Stéphane. No, no. What the hell, man? Come on.
Don't do this. Are you serious? It's over there.
Over there. We're going over there.
There. On the left, at number 46. Come on.
Are you sure?  I'm positive.
Think about it.
Have you ever seen people get deported?
Those poor ladies carrying all their bags and clattering pans,
always politely saying, "Excuse me, please."
Keep walking.
"Please. I'm French like you. Let me stay in France."
And the others answer, "No, you're not French."
"Listen how you talk."
Have you ever seen that? It's tragic.
That makes me want to cry when the poor lady says,
"Oh, I'm sorry, I have the papers." Go on. "No, you don't," they tell her.
France, land of poets.
Charles Baudelaire, Victor Hugo, Alfred de Musset,
and the list goes on and on.
Being here today fills me with enormous pride and a profound sense of honor…
to pay homage and inaugurate with you
this new facility.
The Francky Vincent Senior Center,
after the man we already call the King of Souk.
King of Zouk.
Uh, King of Zouk, to be exact.
The amazing singer of…
"Alice, It Slips."
Thanks a lot.
Pardon me. Some drinks are available inside.
A few refreshments.
To what do we owe the honor of your visit, Mr. President?
It's rare to see you in such a modest village.
Actually, we'd like to offer you…
prime minister.
Are you having trouble with Mrs. Douanier?
That's too bad.
You seemed to get along so well.
Ahem, well, we still get along really well,
except that we're offering you Matignon.
Let's do the legislative elections together
and keep the far right from advancing.
That's a plan that goes smoothly, and everyone's happy.
What do you think, Jérôme?
It's a huge responsibility. Mmhmm.
But when the republic is at stake… Hmm.
…one must make sacrifices.
Wow. That's so well put. Amazing.
And so true.
I accept. But…
I would prefer it if he asked me.
I've just asked you for the both of us.
No.  Considering…
He'd like I heard.
Okay, go ahead. Ask the question, then.
Would you like to be my prime minister?
I couldn't hear.
Okay, would you like to be my prime minister?
Now, I heard it, but…
It was aggressive. Yes, and poorly articulated.
Okay. Would you like to be my prime minister?
I'd be delighted, Mr. President.
But I'm warning you, don't mess with me on social matters.
You can count on me.
We did it.
We're in power. Congratulations. Well done.
"Well done." Are you stupid? No.
I don't give a fuck about Matignon.
Prime minister is an ejection seat.
What I want, is the Élysée.
So why did you accept?
Because over there, in Matignon, I'll be able to take that moron down.
That's right.
I'll organize new elections. It'll be Cognard or me.
It'll be me.
Come on, you can't be suggesting a coup, right?
You know, politics is like andouillette sausage.
When they're well prepared, they always smell like shit.
Do you have a problem with that?
Hmm?
No. Excellent.
Stéphane, that's not possible. Andréï is the most despicable person.
You can't do this.
What do you prefer? The far right? Honestly, I don't know.
Well, I know.
Very well, I resign.
You can't do that.
Have you considered Iranian women whose brothers forbid them from going out?
What's your point? Think hard. There is a point.
We lost them.
Who?
Marion and Aimé.
They were at the hotel,
and then all of a sudden we completely lost contact
and their phones aren't picking up.
Maybe they don't have a signal.
No, that's impossible.
Aimé's phone is a secure line, so that means he always has signal.
Unless there's a crisis.
So that means they're Together?
No. No, they're not together. It's impossible.
I was gonna say "in danger," Mo.
That's better. In danger.
I mean And if I may, Mr. President,
with everything that's happening in the West Indies,
there's a lot of defiance toward the government.
Yeah. My point is, we really must act fast.
It's not safe.
We gotta find her.
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Screaming, "One day, one day" ♪
♪ Hey, hey, one day ♪
♪ "I will be the president" ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪