A NETFLIX SERIES
It's 7:59 p.m.,
and the faces of the two candidates for the second vote
will be revealed to all.
Five, four,
three,
two, one.
Stéphane Blé and Corinne Douanier will move on to the second round
of the presidential election.
Regardless of the results in two weeks, it's a big moment,
because in two weeks,
France will have either its first Black president
or its first female president.
We are going to make you the first Black French president.
Mashallah.
THREE MONTHS EARLIER
We are happy to present you
with a special presidential breakfast show on 79
with the frontrunner in the polls.
Welcome, Éric Andréï. We will, of course, discuss your plans…
Yeah.
♪ I'm the tower of Pisa My tower smells like piss ♪
♪ With hair that looks just like Regis I look just like a penis ♪
♪ They're all illuminati Come on, ask Mimie Mathy ♪
♪ I'm not a fool, that's a bet And I swear on Namek… ♪
Oh, hey. You're wearing shoes in the bedroom.
Come on. Hey.  Yes, just a second. Sorry.
Babe, hey, you're throwing my things!  I need to get to the salon.
Remember, two o'clock tomorrow, the gyno appointment.
Hmm. Me, forget?
I'll be there, yeah.
Our first IVF appointment. Like I'd forget.
Be on time!
♪ At night, I vegetate Misplaced like Vegeta ♪
♪ 93 is the street, guys Time for you to get wise! ♪
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION OFFICIAL CAMPAIGN, FIRST ROUND
The planet burns.
Its killers are men, and when I say "men," I don't mean mankind as a whole.
I mean it's men with penises.
Their phallus, their balls, their member.
Their junk, their dick.
Need I go on?
The patriarchy is leading our world to its demise.
Hey, you're exaggerating.
No, no, no. Exaggeration's past.
This is about our very survival now. Whoa.
On April 10th, cast your vote for ecofeminism.
My dear compatriots, it's an upsurge.
Prices, unemployment, poverty.
Even temperatures are climbing!
Our response is obvious.
Kick all the Arabs out. Wow.
Citizens, cast your votes, and start winning back your pride.
The French are like me.  Oh, no. Not him.
They are generous, caring, welcoming,
brave.
But often, they are also fatigued, drained,
crushed by a political class that is no longer connected to reality.
I must help. How?
I've taken action as mayor.
I've invested funds, specifically for our youth.
You just butchered the budgets, liar. So, on April 10th, vote for a "yes."
Yes to our French courage. Yes to our French ambition and generosity.
Yes to a fair Fra
"A fair France." Idiot.
So, he invested. He invested in what, huh?
What are you talkin' about?
RIGHT BY THE BOOTSTRAPS!
GREEN AGAINST ALL
Let's see a pass, cheapskates. Huh?
Boom. See that control?
What's up, Stéphane? I'm good.
With that huge head. Yeah.
Can't call me? I'll call, I promise. I'll call.
Yeah, you better. Just relax.
Stéphane, hey. How are things?
It's pretty bad what you did with the kids' beach vacation.
What did I do, huh? Ibrahim counted down for two months.
You cancelled it. It wasn't me. It was him, girl.
What? He slashed all the budgets.
He closed down the civic center.
What do we do about it? We have to vote. That's it.
Well, yeah, but I And not for that guy.
Not for president. Not for mayor. Nah.
He's garbage! Garbage. That's right.
Right, be safe, girl. Always.
Stay in touch. Yeah, of course.
Oh, yeah. Now the monitor's late. Look at that.
Hey, get up! What is this? Cómo estás?
What's up? You guys cool? All good.
You clearly don't do your own laundry.
Where's my phone?  Phone?
Took it?  Eat and out.
You're paranoid, hey?  What's in your pocket there, bro?
Lamine, eat, get to class. What I thought.
Give it back. It's fine.
They were bustin' my balls, so I quit. You what?
They looked at me sideways, like I'm the first Black guy they'd seen.
It's bull.
He's pissin' me off, this kid.
Uh, Stéphane, are you
Yo, Stéphane, just don't. Yes, hello.
Ms. Sandalgian?
It's Stéphane Blé, monitor for Lamine.
Yeah, he'll be comin'. There was just a minor issue.
But he'll be there. Knock it off. Just hang up, all right?
WWhy is he late?
Uh, he's late because, um, his father just, uh…
just passed away, regrettably.
He passed away, yes.
It's a real tragedy in African culture. It's a blow.
In the West too, huh? Okay, well, I see.
It's This is the last time he'll run late to class, all right?
I swear.
Well, I mean that his father won't be passing away twice.
I'm sorry. That's not funny. I'm sorry.
Yeah, uh…
Yeah, he'll head over. Thanks.
Yo, that's crazy.  Just eat and go.
Hey, Stéphane, this orange juice sucks.
Are you serious?
Have I not been providing for you?
You better start doing it yourself, then. I mean, your dad's been in prison.
You should be selfsufficient.
I'm sorry, he what?
They told him his dad joined the army. Yeah, he's in the army.
Yeah, yeah, in the army.
Doing pushups, training.  Why bring up prison?
Clearly, when I talk about prison, I mean prison of the mind, obviously.
The first prison is all mental. Hey, let's go.
Andréï's talking himself up. He what?
That mayor. Who does he think he is?
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTIONS ANDRÉÏ: CAMPAIGNING IN THE FIELD
You're a frontrunner, two months from the presidential election,
but you've got harsh critics, and left saying you're rightwing.
Hello, madam.
Yes, yes, I know what they say. I'm left.
It's really absurd rubbish, and I can explain that.
My personal brand, I propose, is really a new left wing,
one that's modern.
A left that's not scared to push up sleeves
and get some work done.
That's the left I want to flourish.
Quién está trabajando aquí? I'm sorry?
Yes, I'm bilingual. Surprised?  Oh!
Stéphane! How are you, sir? I didn't recognize you.
Stéphane works at the youth center.
Superb work effort, Stéphane, truly. Cut the bullshit.
Okay? You know what we all want.
Right.  Respect.
Don't make living around here a kind of handicap.
We don't want that. We don't want that.
Well said. Of course. Well said.  We want the same thing!
I completely understand. You're right.
ButBut I want the same things, just like you all.
Especially since I lived here. My life was in the 'hood.
The Republic gave me everything. I wanna give in return.
Give in return or take everything from us?
Okay.
We have to go.  Tell him!
All you've done in five years… No. Go on, please.
…is cut the budget for all our community associations.
And you tripled the budget for video surveillance.
No, but, I
You know, sir, I can say that Don't call me sir, all right?
Just stop it. All right.
You've known me for years, Éric.
Can you quit putting on a show? It's for the cameras.
Don't keep putting on a show. You're correct.
You are correct here, friend. You are. Don't pretend like we're buddies, please.
You need to respect people. Uh, well, listen to me. Listen to me.
IfIf elected, I will definitely support…  We don't wanna listen to you!
…young professionals. That's how we help. Right, "professionals."
Being doctors, lawyers, engineers. Not people like us, huh?
We work in kitchens. Nothing left to say, right?
Put on your aprons, guys. No, no, no. Stéphane.
Stéphane, now, just one thing at a time. We need to pace things.
Hey, nobody's scared of rolling up sleeves, Éric.
Believe me.  Yeah, tell him!
Yes, but I'm just saying That's right, nobody.
When you're getting fucked over working, sleeves don't matter.
Whoa!
That's well said.  Hey. Wait, wait.
Are you looking for a slogan for your campaign?
I got one for you.
I can't wait to hear it. Go ahead.
It's "Liberty, equality, brotherhood."
Whoa!
All right, salaam.  Mr. Andréï, over here.
Mr. André No, no. No comment, no.
No, no, no.  Thank you very much.
Your job is at risk.
You're better off having a few kids,
instead of acting like a moron for the cameras.
How's that goin'?
Guess how many grandkids Jeanette has.
Eleven. Twelve.
Amen.
Say "amen"!
Amen. Twelve grandchildren.
And me, zero.
Well, we've been, uh… Well, Marion  Yes, we are, but it's hard.
We're doing everything, Simone, I swear, you know, but
You don't desire Marion now, huh? Huh?
She's gained some weight recently, but she's still beautiful.
Mom, that's… Your father, rest in peace…
He's not actually dead. He should be.
His soldier had problems some nights. Wow.
You can talk to me about it.
Uhhuh.  But it's not…
I mean, having a kid is a lot of pressure.
And financially, it's been really hard.
I'm still paying off the business loan on the salon
I talk to her about a child, she talks about a loan.
Hey, it's typical from Beninese. She's not Beninese. She's Senegalese.
Togolese, Beninese, they all love their money, right?
What's that?
Uh, is this a friend, Mom?
Oh!  This is Jeanette. She's my close church friend.
Mm.  Her husband is a bad man.
Mmhmm. She'll stay at your place for now.
Huh?  I don't have room at mine.
I'm sorry, but that's not possible, Simone, because, you know,
at the moment, in the bedroom, we're doing the whole, um…
What's it called, Stéphane? Hey, Stéphane.
You're the one handling it. Stéphane.  Hold on.
I don't know a single person here
who's scared of rolling up sleeves, believe me, Éric.
When you're getting fucked over, sleeves don't matter.
Stéphane Blé is a monitor in a community center
in a housing project,
and seems perfectly ready to challenge Éric Andréï directly.
Yes, absolutely a nightmare for the candidates that are on campaign.
Random guy comes along and just dynamites a visit.
Apparently, the man's no longer anonymous.
The media machine has been quite busy developing "Blémania."
The guy is trending on Twitter. It looks like he's got good punchlines.
So, we asked a polling company,
just as a joke really, to run a little test,
in the perspective of the presidential election,
should he ever run.
How do you think he scored?
One percent?  No, four percent.
Four percent for a twominute segment on TV?!
If you relate that to the electorate,
well, that's about two million voters.
Two million. That's crazy. Two million?
See how lucky you are to be with my son?
Two million!
Wow, Stéph. You're in the paper!  Yeah.
It's crazy. You're right there. Look at that.
How are you? I'm good.
We just saw you on TV yesterday with the mayor.
Oh, thank you. Thanks, Auntie. You were topnotch.
Hey, you totally owned the mayor, huh? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Great, man. Thanks, thanks.
Stéphane!
Stéphane, some questions. Are you gonna run for mayor?
So, what's your perception of secularism in France?
Are you going to run opposite Andréï?
No, I'm just a citizen who's sick of getting my ass kissed
every five years or so, and getting boned otherwise.
That's my position. Any more questions?
Okay, no more questions.  Is it
Okay, no more comments. Wait. We have more questions.
No. Thank you. Bye. Bye. Thank you.
All right, come on.
Who are you?
William Crozon.
I've directed campaigns for about 15 years.
I've helped elect greats, the best.
And also idiots. But our politics are my life.
And you, my guy… you're unique.
Just between us, you must be sick of all the white politicians
that fuck with us.
It's because no one represents guys like us two.
Are you Turkish?
Because you don't look Black, man. Huh?
All right, you just Arabized.
No, you pleb, you Islamized
the grandnephew of the great Aimé Césaire.
Huh? Oh, yeah? No big deal. The inventor of Négritude.
Yes, yes. I know, I know. Yeah, well, whatever.
Yeah, seeing you, despite the teeth, you're perfect.
Have you been in jail?
No. You married?
Yeah. That's perfect.
Any kids? No.
Get some. Lots.
Are you gay?
What the hell, man?
Man, you're bein' crazy, right? I'm not gay, all right?
Okay, yeah, you got a problem with that.
But just wait. I'm from the 'hood. I know how people feel about gays.
No. No. And I don't appreciate what you're insinuating here.
Uh, the guys in the 'hood have evolved.
It's not like you're making out. Mmhmm.
On my block, there's a family. Hmm?
Uh, there's two brothers, and the two are gay men.
And Arabs to boot. Wow.
And?
Well, the same family.
Okay. And?
There's two. There's two, I mean…
That's my bad. There. You need to change that, okay?
Get rid of all these revolting ideas, because now you've got credibility.
You're great, you're unique. Me, I've got savvy and a strategy.
I've got savvy too. Yeah, all right.
But not as much. Now, listen to me.
Two Black guys, the two of us, in the Elysée, my guy.
You get me? The new Barack and Michelle.
Just hang on one second. Boom!
Stop right there.
Who's Barack and who's Michelle in all this?
This guy. Go on, just elaborate for me.
You have a real problem with that. It's crazy.
I don't wanna bang you, man.
I want to transform you into the president
of France, my guy.
But I'm not in politics anymore. You were in politics?
Well, yeah, back in the day, with my band State Thugs.
We were all dedicated.
But that's behind me now. It's over.
It's not behind you.
The guy I just saw taking down Andréï has that rage.
He made me angry, trying to lecture us, you know.
All the real solutions rise from below.
Oh, this is it. That's right.
Creole. I was raised in the Antilles.
It sneaks out when I get angry. How it is. Remember the commonwealths?
Oh, no, I remember the Antilles, man. Of course.
No, of course.
Hmm. Mm.
We'll do great things. I swear. I can see it now.
Because you represent the block. You represent the voiceless.
You represent those who feel oppressed, those who feel hopeless.
All those guys, me, livin' in Sarcelles.
You know Sarcelles? Totally.
You know CMurder, Give, all that? Pfft.
Yeah? My guys on the block!
Uh, but where in Sarcelles?
Uh, uh, next to Next to, uh, CMurder, yeah.
We all They all But where?
Which area were you in?  Uh…
Tartier, Tartlet, Tartelet?
Is that right, "Tartlet"?
Oh shit.
Hey, you have my card, right? My card!
The Tarterets! Shit.
Yes?  Seriously, what are you doing?
I'm at the clinic waiting. I know, sorry. I'll be right there.
You're such a pain. Don't worry. Soon.
If this is gonna work, you need to get serious.
Shit. I'm waiting here, and you're not answering.
It takes two to make a life. If you're not up for it, say so.
Stéph?
Stéph? Are you there?
Ah, my cuz. Why are you hiring Lamine? Bro.
What's wrong with you?
How many ways can I explain we don't talk about that here?
Are you mad?
The kid's in a training program. He has to finish. Please.
Seriously. All right, come on.
Djibril, say hi to your uncle.
Hi, Djibril! What's up?
I don't give a crap.
He's not working for you. Lamine's the same as the others, bro.
The boy wants food in his fridge, same as the rest.
No, he's different, and for years now,
Marion and I have looked out for his best interests.
Please.
Fine, I'll pay him for today and send the kid home.
Good? All right?  Okay. Thanks, bro.
All right, we'll begin with ten to 12 days of hormone shots.
Then we'll begin collecting your oocytes,
and while we're at it, your husband's sperm.
Or your, uh… From your…
I mean, is there a donor? Your husband?
Supposedly, yes. I'm here, I'm here!
Ah. How's everything going?
Hi, hon. Mwah. You're that guy on the TV.
Hmm?  On TV.
It's you? Yeah.
Impressive. You murdered Andréï.
If you ran for office, I'd for sure vote for you.
Him, campaigning? Oh, please. Almost missed our meeting, didn't you?
It's just that I had an issue.
I'll tell you later, but I'm here 200 percent, promise.
Right here, my love.
You mean that, right? Yeah.
You mean you know what'll happen? Yes.
Because I need to give myself hormonal injections daily.
It'll be quite hard, obviously.  Mmhmm.
You have to provide some, uh, well…
Uh, some Your sperm.
Sperm, and… Ah.
…you're also gonna have to make sure it's fresh by tasting it.
So, uh What?
Oh, please. It's fine. Don't be a prude.
You just put a… a bit on your lips, like this.
A bit like gloss, you know? Just to see if it has any flavor. Simple.
But if that's too hard, you just put it right here.
Like a bottle, you know? Yeah, a bottle.
There. And it's not that crazy. Everybody's done it. It's not like, uh…
Yeah, I've tasted it. That's true.
I can say that, yeah.
What's four percent? Four percent isn't serious.
My mother could beat that. It's four percent!
Still, he's stealing it from you, the four percent, right?
Yeah, I know. That's right.
Fifteen years. He's been there for 15 years!
And it was me who got him this job.
Me!
If I still worked in the Interior, I'd red flag him, huh?
Blé doesn't matter. No, he does matter.
The guy is just hot air. That's all he is.
So, tomorrow, informally invite him to your meeting.
Easy.  No way.
We're fine, we'll make it, but we must maintain voter diversity.
"Diversity." You're pissing me off with your diversity!
Diversity is everywhere with you! Madness!
Under my flyers, in my campaign. I'll have to go to bed with diversity!
I'm a giver. I give. Where's my gratitude?
They spit on gratitude! I'm leftwing, true, but I have limits.
There. You wanna spend all morning on this?
No. Good.
But I needed to Yeah, yeah.
Tomorrow, you'll give him some candy and move on ahead.
Hmm. Yeah?
Yeah. There's more important things.
Yes, my platform. Well, yes.
They vote for platforms, and they also vote for…
a presence, an air, a look.
With his face, I like my chances.
Yeah, but he's got style, a "thing."
While you…
Yeah, me?
We'll fix it.
All right, then.
Did you see that yesterday? Ibrahim got smashed off his board.
Oh, yeah? He got hit?
Yeah, he did. I swear.  Well, he is a loser.
He went flying. I'll call you back.
Yeah.  Did he actually?
Hey!  Shit!
Don't you move! Hold it! Stay right there!
Stéphane.
Lamine just got picked up by the cops. What?
Yeah, he got caught. Just now.
Just now? Yeah, they just got him.
Shit.
What are you doing? Go on now. Coming with you.
I've told you three times!
His home situation's complicated. That's why I'm here.
And if you're not his mom or dad, or court guardian,
he can't possibly go with you.
Move on.
Oh, come on, dude. Next. Ma'am.
No way I'm moving without Lamine!
He can't miss his course or he'll get kicked out.
Fine. That's fine.
As an outraged citizen, your behavior is unacceptable.
I want the person in charge of you. That's it. Now. Congrats.
Are you talkin' to me like that?
I'm sorry?
If rights were violated, the shit will hit the fan!
Every person in here has the right to a confidential meeting with a lawyer.
Article 631 of the criminalprocedure code.
You want Internal Affairs on your ass?
Have a good night. Thanks.
What are you doing here? Uh…
I'm gonna get you and the kid out. Don't worry.
And, um…
between us, it's pretty cool you're locked up here.
It's like Mandela. Fabulous.
Hold on. What about Mandela?
Oh, Mandela? He's Black, just like we are.
Twentyseven years in jail. While you've had two hours? A bit less?
Huh, close. An hour forty. Half an hour. An hour and a half.
Anyway, you've done time.
Suffering as a political prisoner,
just like him!
I'll use this to stir up the neighborhood. I'll appeal to the press.
And once you're out, you will announce your candidacy for president.
Oh, man, no! Hey!
I said no. I can't be doing that, man.
I've got my job.
I want a kid with my wife. I can't be doing this stuff.
What world do you wanna give your kid? Tell me.
A world where as soon as he steps out of line,
he'll get taken down?
A world where he gets locked up just because he's Black?
That kind of world?
Is that Creole again? It's Frantz Fanon, a quote.
When he bounced to Algeria for training thethe…
The guys for the Algerian revolution. Did the Algerians speak Creole?
I think there were speeches later in French and that's probably
Look.
What is missing in the world today, huh?
It's hope, man. Tell me, how is hope born?
It's just a glint.
And that little glint…
could be you.
Or maybe someone else. Who knows?
That's what's interesting, I find. Right?
I'll get you out, man.
Liberate Stéphane Blé! Liberate Stéphane Blé!
Liberate Stéphane Blé!
Yeah! Let him go! Liberate Stéphane Blé!
Liberate Stéphane Blé! Liberate Stéphane Blé!
Liberate Please, everyone.
I'm gonna ask you to disperse now. Yeah?
"Disperse." Sure. Go on.
No justice, no peace.
Liberate Stéphane Blé!
Liberate Stéphane Blé! Yeah! Why, huh?!
We'll be here until Stéphane Blé has been freed.
Fine. Okay, gas 'em all.
Huh?  Liberate…
Go ahead. Gas them all. No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no! Liberate Stéphane Blé!
They're gonna gas us! He's gonna gas us! He's gonna gas us!
Liberate  Ah!
POLICE STATION
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, slidin' through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, slidin' through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, slidin' through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
He's out. Stéphane!
Stéphane!
Oh, shit.
Have you decided?
What d'you think?
Well,
you've always said I should dream big.
And, uh…
And I think, really, president sounds great.
Dude, no. You'll never be president.
Hey, this is France, not the United States.
Here, they like Black folk if they're funny,
if they bring home the World Cup,
or if they do gospel, period.
Okay, all right. So I'm not funny.
I don't dance much. I don't do gospel. Okay?
I'm not really a president,
so I wanna put the spotlight on real voters.
People. People from real life. Basically, people like us both.
But I need you as a partner. Mandela without Winnie isn't Mandela.
Mmhmm.
You doin' all right?
You know they ended up getting divorced?
Yeah?
You're terrible. I knew.
Of course I did.
Hey, we're so much stronger.
Than Mr. Mandela? What? With you, yeah.
Okay.
I'm in, if you're in for us.
You'll give me the injections.
All the injections. I'm needlephobic. Be at every single gyno consult.
And be on time, because I know you. Right.
And most importantly, please…
don't become a politician.
Me?
You. Me?
You! Me?!
You!
Stéphane Blé.
Mm.
Thank you.
The reason I'm here today, everyone,
is to tell you all that I'm running in the presidential elections
of the French Republic!
I'll admit, the guy you see here running for president, it's crazy.
But for me, what's most crazy
is that 70 percent of the French don't vote!
One day every five years, that's our power, that's what we get!
What I want is to give us power every day of the damn year!
Amen!
Amen!  That's right!
People here know me. I'm a social worker in the community.
And the work I do with our kids
is what I'd like to do, but I wanna do it on a national scale.
Yeah!
Yeah! Let's go!
The real problem with all these elections is
Mr. Durandeau.
How are you, sir?  I'm fine.
Are you watching this? Mmhmm.
You hear this?
They don't know about family allowances. They were never without a mom or dad.
They never had to share a room.
This is my latest protégé's speech,
announcing that he's running.
Look at him. I think he's gonna kill it. I heard about him. And you want?
Would you like to keep Andréï out of this match?
How would that happen?
Well, you help me to look for sponsors,
and my guy will steal around seven to eight percent,
we siphon the left votes,
and Andréï bombs out quick, and your road has been cleared.
Mmhmm. And in exchange? Easy.
I want a job. Is that all?
You've got some nerve. Interested or what?
I'll get some sponsors, and we'll speak again, hmm?
Amen!
And what I wanna prove is
that you can be Black, you can come from the projects,
not wear a suit, and love France, yo!
Because really, France is yours! And France belongs to all of us!
Blé, president! Blé, president!
Blé, president!
Blé, president! Blé, president! Blé, president!
Blé, president! Oh! Ah!
Blé, president! Ay!
Blé, president! Blé, president!  Oh! Yeah!
Blé, president! Blé, president!
Blé, president! Blé, president!
Blé, president! Blé, president! Blé…
Yeah! Ha, ha, ha! Audi B, my State Thugs!
My State Thugs! 2005, the year of success!
Stay ready out there!
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Look me in the eyes Tryin' to make yourself rich ♪
♪ Come on, suck on this cock Your dad'll die of shock ♪
♪ Marianne, you whore Are we in love or are we at war? ♪
♪ Sell me on Republic Get me hard as a brick ♪
♪ Marianne, you slut Know you like 'em uncut ♪
♪ Blue, white, blood red Know you heard what I said ♪
♪ Blue, white, bullshit Now it's time to get lit ♪
What is this?  ♪ Where the sun'll never hit ♪
♪ Not like I'm fucking homosexual ♪ Yeah, but outta context, it's
♪ Audi B's on the beat With assault that's textual ♪
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Look me in the eyes Tryin' to make yourself rich ♪
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Come on, suck on this cock Your dad'll die of shock ♪
♪ Marianne, you whore Are we in love or we at war? ♪
♪ Look me in the eyes Tryin' to make yourself rich ♪
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Come on, suck on this cock Your dad'll die of shock ♪
♪ Marianne, you whore Are we in love or are we at war? ♪
♪ Sell me on Republic Get me hard as a brick ♪
♪ Marianne, you slut I know you like 'em uncut ♪
♪ Blue, white, blood red Know you heard what I said ♪
♪ Blue, white, bullshit Now it's time we get lit ♪
♪ Shove their Marseillaise Where the sun'll never hit ♪
♪ It's not like I'm fucking homosexual ♪
♪ Audi B's on the beat With assault that's textual ♪
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Look me in the eyes Tryin' to make yourself rich ♪
♪ Come on, suck on this cock Your dad'll die of shock ♪
♪ Marianne, you bitch Marianne, you bitch ♪
♪ Look me in the eyes Tryin' to make yourself rich ♪
♪ Come on, suck on this cock Your dad'll die of shock ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪