So, we pieced together the events of their night.
It starts at 7:30 p.m., dinner at the Rose Garden restaurant.
Then they booked a spa treatment at the Blue Parrot at 10:18 p.m.
Then they went back to the presidential suite,
where they ordered… Ah.
…a bottle of champagne around 12:11 a.m.
Then we completely lost contact with them at 2:33 a.m.
I don't give a shit about what they were doing!
What I want is to find her, to know where she is.
Very well, but I can't know everything so…
Send in anyone you want. I don't care.
SWAT teams, the army, or anyone else who can get the job done.
I just need her found.
Sorry to interrupt,
but, uh, if they drank a whole bottle of champagne
and then, uh, turned off their phones at 2:30 a.m.,
maybe there's another angle to consider. No. No.
No.
There is.
No, Yasmine, you're mistaken.
You're mistaken. He's gay.
Exactly.
I'm sorry, you're completely incorrect. He's not gay at all.
Yeah, for sure, he's totally gay.
I hired him. I know what I'm talking about.
I know what I saw in him.
Then again, I'm thinking, the First Lady being kidnapped,
from an electoral point of view, it's incredible.
People feel sorry for him. They vote for him again. It's great.
What? don't look at me like I'm some asshole, all right?
It's a strategy like any other. It's not that bad.
We'd secure reelection, no doubt about it.
No matter what, this can't be leaked
because if the people who kidnapped her hear about this, they might freak out.
They could send us an ear through the post mail.
Or a toe. That's what I would do. Send a toe.
For what?
If you're missing a toe, you can't escape.
True. He's right. If you're missing a foot, maybe.
A missing toe, you can still run. It'll affect your balance.
You can't run as well, but you can run. But without an ear, you'd stagger, zigzag.
No, that's for cats.
I can cut off your ear, see how you deal with it.
I got it. I'll go find them myself.
I'm sorry, but you can't disappear like that.
You have to take care of the upcoming elections from here.
What will I tell them if you're gone?
Tell them I'm campaigning in the West Indies.
You take care of Andréï. You're coming with me.
No, because I believe that I'm much more useful on the mainland.
It would be a good idea for Yasmine to accompany you.
And I'll deal with Andréï.
Aren't you from the West Indies?
I'm from Grands Fonds SainteAnne. It's like an island within an island.
Almost a different Creole language. These guys don't understand each other.
You're coming.  Yeah, okay.
Can I come with?  No.
We have to go with someone else. Someone who knows the ghetto well.
I know someone, but you won't like it.
Who do you know?
Someone.
Who is it?
Uh, I can't say.
Say it.
I won't say it.
Well, we're gonna find out. Just shoot.
No, no, it's a secret.
How old are you? What kind of secret is that?
I have a secret. I'm gonna tell a secret.
No, don't say it.
I'm gonna tell a secret too.  No, don't say it.
Fine. Tell your secret first. After, I'll tell mine. Not.
How old are you, Mo?
Um…
36 years old.
Wow, he actually had to think and do the math.
REPRESENT
Mr. Désiré Guigui.
Quit the namedropping, dude.
Oh yeah.
All right.
President, huh?
You made it, my man.
Yeah, but here's the thing…
I won't lie to you, though.
The inauguration thing kind of hurt my feelings.
You could've sent me an invite. We're family.
You kidding? After the crazy shit you pulled on me?
Are we family or not?  We're family.
I couldn't. Get over it. You could've… invited me.
Yeah.
All right, it's okay. No worries. I'm here.
You gonna give me the tour? No, I don't have time for that.
We think Marion has been kidnapped in Guadeloupe with her bodyguard.
Oh my God.
And?
I know you know lots of people there, I thought you could help me out.
Oh, I see. All right. So you didn't want to see me.
I'm here to lend a hand. No, it's great to see you, Désiré.
Stop it, come on. It's always the same with you.
Listen up, bro.
Guadeloupe right now, it's chaotic over there.
It's not welcoming.
Oh yeah? Think the street is bad here?
It's a playground compared to there.
They don't have streets. It's a jungle. You hear gunshots at breakfast. At dawn.
Bang! Oh fuck.
Where and when exactly did she disappear?
She disappeared at two in the morning in a hotel called the Blue Parrot.
Hmm. I'll help you out.
No worries. Got guys over there and everything.
We can go, no problem.
But we have to take the presidential plane.
Gotta save time, you know?
In terms of security and customs, all that.
Yeah. Round trip, though?
Yeah. Like, for real?
Yeah. Let's go. Come on.
Thanks a lot, coz. Seriously, man.
No problem, brother. We family. We family.
["Illusion Sur Mauna Loa" by Varnish La Piscine playing]
♪ I don't wanna wake up ♪
I've got shivers. I'm home.
All right, guys.
I have a couple of phone calls to make real quick.
I'll meet you at the hotel, all right?
We don't have much here, but we give.
We're generous.
They don't have shoes, they walk barefoot.
But they give. They give.
Son of a bitch!
What did he say?
"Counia manmanw." It's, um…
Like, "I know your mother."
Oh, cool.  Yeah.
Counia manmanw!  Thanks.
These accras are too spicy.
I think the heat is starting to affect my vocal cords, aren't they?
Are you sure you don't want to try one? Accras, anyone?
No. All right, listen up, we go straight to the hotel
to see if we can get any intel.
I want to find her quick.
What's this?
My West Indies are here to greet you.
Are you sure about that? They seem pretty pissed off.
Yeah, they're pissed off, but with good vibes.
WILL YOU ADDRESS OUR PROBLEMS?
Here, it's Everything's very exuberant, colorful. It's very…
Okay, please, talk to them. Tell them to calm down, please.
Me? Yeah, go ahead.
Been a while since I've spoken Creole. I speak the old Creole.
Talk to them. Tell them to calm down. Yeah, all right. I'll do it.
Um…
"Listen…" Okay, wait. Hold on.
Okay, okay.
Resignation! Whoa!
Hey, calm down!
They seem really angry. What is it they're asking for?
We speak English, sir.
These guys, there's the president, he's good.
Hey yo! Watch out now!
Is it broken? Where?
All right. I'm going to speak to the president,
to see if he wants to hear your requests, all right?
They're not being receptive. Come on, let's get out of here.
The guy's hand was this close to me. Like, I mean, like, one inch.
Please get out of the way, let me do it.
What are you doing? The dude in orange is nuts.
The president will speak now. Today.
Listen up. Thank you.
What's wrong? What's happening, brothers?
What do you mean, "my brothers"? You're Ivorian, man.
Oh. Whoa. Okay, fair enough. Yeah, it's true.
But I'm also the president, all right? I know there are some problems here.
I came for that reason, to resolve everything.
And it starts with your votes at the legislative elections,
if you want me to be able to take action, all right?
We're gonna vote. We're gonna vote for Cognard.
Cognard! Cognard! Cognard! Cognard!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Have you lost your damn mind?
You don't know how crazy that fool is? Of course we do.
In fact, he's… He's like us. He's angry.
Yeah, you talk and talk, but you don't do anything.
About the chlordecone. What will you do about that?
I don't understand. What's chlordecone?
It's Creole. It means…
Something like… "It's totally insane."
It's "chlordinsane." All right, makes more sense.
Hold on.
It's a pesticide that's poisoning us.
Ah, it means that too. Good to know.  Andy!
Come here and show him your colon cancer.
I don't want to.
Get undressed right now!
Take it off! Take it off! Come on!
No, no, no. We have to get out of here.
Start the car, start the car! Come on! Come on, come on. Come on!
Mr. Prime Minister,
I admit that we've all been displeased by the animosity of Mrs. Douanier,
your predecessor.
Or should I say predecesstress?
In her case, the masculine prevails, in my opinion.
Thanks.
About the president's desire to withdraw troops from Africa,
I personally think it's pure madness.
It's not pure madness, General.
It's complete bullshit.
This whole notion of their repentance is absurd.
Colonization.
No. I don't side with that camp.
Mm.
Good to hear.
However, General…
for quite some time now,
I've been hearing certain rumors that are…
very unsettling.
A kind of anger that rumbles and frightens me.
So I was wondering.
Will you be able to keep a cool head
when the time comes to choose between order
and chaos?
Chaos? Chaos.
Whether it comes from the street or perhaps from the Élysée.
As commander in chief of the armed forces, I owe him my loyalty.
I know all this, but…
But if France was ever in danger…
I would always side with France.
I mean, the real France.
That's a relief for me.
Good.
Let's go see those CAESAR howitzers. Everyone says they're great.
Be my guest.
Mo, you'll check the hotel security cameras.
Okay.
Come with me, William. We'll search her room.
Good idea, but first, I have to deal with something.
You're coming.  Okay.
BLUE PARROT HOTEL &amp; SPA
What the fuck?
No, no.
Oh no.
Jesus Christ.
I'm sorry.
Damn it, that knocked me out.
Whoa! Whoa! Ooh!
Wow. I'm not sure what they're adding to the accras anymore,
but they don't taste like the West Indies I know.
Sorry for the… I couldn't find anything.
Yeah, me neither. It's started to affect my vocal cords.
Oh my God. Yeah, yeah. I know.
What's wrong with you?
I just… You need to get a full checkup in Paris.
I can't eat Creole cuisine. Not just the food. You got a problem.
You think? Anyway, I've got the rest of our program.
Yeah. Hold up. I know what it is, William.
What? We're gonna find Marion.
We're gonna look for Marion, that's for sure.
But now, the top priority is the legislative elections.
All right? It's the campaign. The campaign, the campaign, okay?
So I've set up a visit to this dope little distillery.
It's gonna be great, you'll see. Enough with the clichés.
We're in the West Indies, so it's all about the rum and zouk now.
Is that all? Since we're here, let's do something useful.
Like, how about we go to PointeàPitre
and inaugurate a memorial for Aimé Césaire?
Something that holds significance for us. I see. I'm the one with clichés?
The epitome of the French West Indies cliché is that dude.
And plus, I can't stand Aimé Césaire.
Are you serious? I thought you were his greatnephew.
I am his greatnephew. So what? It's no excuse.
He's created negritude.
Don't you have any issues with that?
As if an Arab came up with Arabitude,
or a Jew with Jewitude.
Yeah. Isn't it absurd?
That's not my West Indies. What are your West Indies?
I'll tell you. Fine, it's, uh…
My West Indies, it's the guys with the broken teeth.
A bit like… Hang on a sec. Yeah?
Who is it? What the fuck? It's crazy.
Come on. Fuck.
Go ahead.  William, you there?
Yeah, Mo. Any updates?  Yeah.
Man, it's fucked up. It's fucked up.
Is there news?  Marion hooked up with her bodyguard.
Get out of here.  Honest to God.
Any news? Huh?
Any news? No news.
He didn't find anything.
There's nothing.  What do you mean?
I told you Aimé fucked Marion.
Okay, awesome. Awesome. That's awesome, man.
Does he have news or not?  Don't you understand?
Aimé fucked the First Lady, damn it! He screwed the president's wife.
Sounds good. Hold on.
He wants to know where we're eating, because he's already hungry.
He'd like to eat chicken.
We don't give a shit about chicken. Forget about the chicken.
What? We're looking for Marion, man.
I'm not hungry.
Take three chickens for you,
and we'll have one lobster, one grilled fish, and some accras.
No! No accras. Please, not that!  Accras?
What the fuck are you You're the best.
This guy is obsessed with food.
Désiré has an update.
What is it? All right, let's go meet him.
Don't get too close to the bathroom door.
It's beautiful.
Check that out. The Jet Skis, the guys having a blast.
We're in the middle of the week, man.
We think we're living that fancy Parisian life,
and then, bam, you witness this.
What's that?
It's nothing. Some presents for the homies. It's…
Soft toys. You're a good friend.
Uh, so we localized Marion.
She was last seen at 3:00 a.m. with her bodyguard, getting inside a car.
Uh, but, uh, she didn't seem to be consensual.
Oh, fuck!
As long as she didn't consent, it's all right.
It's all right.
It's fucked up, but we're moving forward.
Anyway, my guy's getting some intel, and in an hour he'll get back to me.
All right, cool. Okay. Great.
It gives us time to go make your speech.
Let's move.
No, sorry, I don't feel like it at all right now.
Let's go, Stéphane. Bring up the "living together" concept.
Um, Guadeloupe getting worse and worse, into near fourthworld status.
"But we're gonna fix this." Blah, blah, blah.
Then we take photos and go. Think about the legislative elections.
Let's go.
Can I take one of the plushies? I have a friend here who has a child.
How old? Six years old.
Only six? No, man.
It's not plushies suitable for his age.
These plushies are something else, you know?
Ah.  They're plushies for…
Adults?  Yeah, for adults.
Okay.  Okay what?
No, I'm sorry. I thought that, uh…  Mmhmm.
You understand, right?
Mr. Mayor.
Hello, everyone.
I know you don't like me, like most French people at the moment.
I was elected, it's true.
And I thought that that was the hardest part, but it's not.
We know damn well, and it's no secret, that as Black folks,
we receive no respect and are often ignored.
Yeah.
If you vote for me in the legislative elections,
I'll bring this message to the world.
And so, "My mouth speaks for those who cannot,
my voice represents the freedom of the hopeless."
It's a quote by Aimé Césaire, people.
Fuck Aimé Césaire!
Told you, Mr. President. Césaire is from Martinique.
We are in Guadeloupe.
White people always do this to us. It's a pain in the ass.
Exactly. It's a pain in the ass bigtime.
Did you mean to take on their accent or make fun of them?
You're out of line. Quit the whole "trying to be cool" thing.
AIMÉ CÉSAIRE SQUARE
I got good and bad news, cousin. Okay, what's the good news?
Marion got snatched up by those Békés. Fuck.
Because of her tax proposal. They took her to an isolated spot.
They're holding her. It's gonna be very tricky.
I only half agree, because it's the Békés. They should be pretty gentle.
All right, so it looks like we've got nothing but bad news.
What's the good news? The good news is, well, she's alive.
That's two good newses for me. Look at the bright side.
She was taken by the Békés, not independentists.
We should be all right…  Hey!
They're extremists, these guys are crazy.
Listen to me, I'm gonna roll with my crew and handle this, no problem.
You have 70% chance to get her back.
Alive?
Alive, 30% chance.
Come on, stop it. What's so funny?
Are you listening to yourself? You're talking nonsense.
They're Békés, guys.
They're as gentle as lambs.  Gentle? They're fucking awful.
These guys are terrible.
Yeah, there was a time when these men became wealthy
off the backs of Black people in ship holds.
They did let people die of thirst in sugarcane fields.
He's full of shit.  Hear me out. They evolved.
Now the 2.0 Békés variant is… Mwah! Seriously?
They have a sense of friendship, a work ethic.
I'm telling you, we're judging them based on a past that's maybe questionable,
even though they did do some cool stuff.
And now we're saying they're awful? I'm shocked.
Okay, let's cut the shit out.
I'm calling in the pros now. I'm done.
I'm telling you, dude… You're a friend of the Békés, huh?
I'm not a friend of the Békés… Yeah.
…but I am keeping an open mind. I'm just
I'll introduce you if you're cool with it. I know a crew of Békés.
I mean, I swear, these guys are… I'm in, man.
Are there girls too?
Let's call Alice to see what she can do.
Even though, I gotta admit… Ugh!
So I studied the area,
and the success rate of the mission is 60%.
Wait, 60% if she's alive?
No, uh…
Alive, it's 20%.
What are you talking about? Even Désiré had estimated 30%.
You see?
Well, I'm not sure.
I'd trust him if I were you.
I don't know who he is, but he seems good.
I kinda like her.
There's no choice. We gotta handle this ourselves.
You're not going anywhere. You're staying here. You're the president.
I don't care, I'll tell them to take me as hostage instead of Marion.
Mr. President, you can't do that. It's suicidal.
Of course, I'm right. You can't do that.
Above all, it's very heroic, Mr. President.
Wait, wait, what the hell is that guy doing here?
"That guy" is your prime minister,
and everything that happens to you, happens to me.
You know that.
I don't understand the defiance you feel toward me.
Oh yeah? But I don't blame you.
It's your own flesh and blood being threatened.
Congratulations on your decision. It's very brave.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
There's something Gaullist about the decisions you make.
This dude.  What the fuck.
Okay. Got the address?
Yeah, buddy. The war is on.
We're going ourselves. Let's go.
It's gonna be tough, but we'll do it.
Obviously, the president is blinded by sadness.
We would be too.
Either way, we need to take strong action with these terrorists.
What terrorists?
The Béké. We must take quick action.
I don't want the tragic events of November 13 to happen again.
Never again. I lost a cousin when that happened.
Really?  Yeah.
Hm.
Excuse me.
Your cousin…
On what side was he?
On my mother's side.
No, I mean, what side? Was he with…
You know…
Or…
"Ah!"
It's a legitimate question.  Yes.
Wait, are you serious?
Either way, either way, the Republic will not negotiate with such terrorists.
I'll go get them all the way down the shithole.
What about the president?
Glory be with him.
Can you leave me for a few minutes, please?
Unbelievable.
Thanks.
Yes, General, it's me.
There's a crisis in PointeàPitre. Let's do something big and forceful.
Fuck.
It's magnificent.
Magnificent. Incredible.
Look, they hired locals.
Yeah, Patricia, look where I am.
It's our dream house.
This place is crazy. There's so much room. It's amazing.
Nice to meet you.
Clément Robicheaux.
Guadeloupean since 1683.
Stéphane Blé. President of France.
I know.
Now that we're here, you can release Marion.
Well, release…
She's not exactly held hostage.
She kinda is, man.
Who's this Black guy who thinks he's free to talk a lot?
What'd he just say? Chill.
No, it's okay, calm down. Chill out. We're among gentlemen,
Everything's gonna be all right.
Yeah. No worries.
Come on, follow me.
I can feel it. Shit is gonna hit the fan.
Calm down. Calm down, guys. Chill out, Désiré.
Chill out. Calm down.
Good evening.
It's so magnificent.
The columns and everything.
Ahem, Mr. President.
For us, the Béké tax you're trying to ratify,
I'll tell you what I think.
For us, it's just one more insult
that we can't tolerate, okay?
Hold on, let me explain because I don't want to seem unlikable.
We've done our part, you know?
We freed the… the "slaves."
All right?
We did it gladly.
We had to pay up, but it's all good.
That was nice of you, thanks.  Yeah. You're welcome.
So, what's the big reward for all our efforts?
First of all, alarmingly high levels of unemployment.
Not related. Right?
Yeah, but populations are undereducated,
A majority of people are illiterate and can't do basic arithmetic.
I even wonder if they know they exist.
For some of them, do they even have a conscience?
Right? That's a question we're entitled to ask.
Then there's rampant insecurity.
Forgive me for saying so, but delinquency's knocking at our doors.
The road up front is a disaster.  Hm.
They drive their horsedrawn carriages on the sidewalks.
Hm. Fuck!
This has to stop. Okay with you?  Hmm.
It's enough. We've had enough.
Also, to add insult to the injury,
the media consistently portray us as deplorable.
Have you noticed the influx of films that are about the servitudes of slaves?
They depict us, without exception, as evil.
Not necessarily.
For example, I'm thinking of a masterpiece.
Gone with the Wind. Have you seen it, sir?
No.  You're well portrayed.
What about you? Watch it. It's fabulous.
I'll check it out. Extraordinary.
Let's be serious for a second. Can we just agree on the fact
that slave owners and slaves are both wrong?
Right? I mean, it's not because someone holds a whip
like they do on all the family pictures,
that they're necessarily bastards.
I mean, come on.
You always wear chains around the neck in the photos
with this look of, you know, "suffering,"
which shows a real lack of modesty, if I may point that out.
Hm.  Does that mean you're victims?
The jury's still out. The jury is still out.
I don't mean to interrupt but, look, I love the photos, they're incredible.
However, the whip, it's still
I mean, it's a mark of domination from your perspective.
It's not, but that's beside the point. A little bit the point.
Not all victims are the same. Okay, but…
Not all victims are the same.  That's not really true.
I'll be clear with you, I'm not asking for the moon,
I'm asking for a little more nuance. There, is that too much to ask?
So about the nuance, uh, business, I think it's a question of point of view.
We've got ourselves some opposing views, yeah?
However, about the Béké tax, by all means, let's talk.
We're not talking anymore. Yeah, but let's avoid…
I want to see my wife. Come on, um…
Let's just talk.
René, go get her.
You speak Creole?  Of course.
SCANNING IN PROGRESS…
TARGET LOCATED
We've arrived on site. Waiting for instructions.
Making an omelet requires breaking eggs.
Prime minister's order.
Engage the target.
Get rid of it all.
Asking for order confirmation.
The risk of collateral damage is high. The president could be among the victims.
Order confirmed.
Uh, Éric?
Are we really doing this?
He can run.
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine, thanks.
You, look at me, you filthy bastard.
What do you think will happen? You can kill us? We won't give in.
Chill.  Got it?
Seriously, he's insane. He chained me.
"Kill us"? Don't pay attention to her. She's lost it.
She's only speaking for herself and doesn't really
They're shooting!
Where's that son of a bitch going?
The terrorists either fled or have been neutralized.
And no sign of the president. I repeat, no sign of the president.
Terrorists have been neutralized.
Mission accomplished, Prime Minister.
Good news, the president is alive.
William, before we leave, I want to talk to the locals.
I've got something to announce. Can you set that up, please?
Okay. And sorry again for what happened.
That's not my French West Indies, you know?
EAT WELL, FOR FREE
Honestly, folks, prices here are insane.
Straightup ridiculous.
I understand why Guadeloupeans are angry.  Yeah!
That's why I made the choice to launch here a pilot version
of my "Eat well, for free" main measure.
Because I want all the women and men of Guadeloupe
to be able to eat healthy and for free from now on.
All this will be financed by the Béké tax, led by my wonderful wife.
And if the French people decide to trust me at the next elections,
I'll extend the measure to the whole country.
Ain't no time for games, you feel me? No unnecessary chatter.
I'm gonna do it. Voilà.
That asshole's not giving up.
He may not wanna give up,
but he's a cuckold.
How about that.
The First Lady of France is having fun.
Who is it?
Her bodyguard.
No way. Yes.
Send all of those, anonymously.
Consider it done.
Now I'm embarrassed by them, I swear.
I don't recognize my homeland, my French West Indies.
It used to be so fraternal there. There were Chinese, Indians, whites…
All right, you can stop now. What?
We know you're not from there.
I… Me not
Me not from the West Indies? Why the hell would you say that?
Hello, Mr. President. Have a safe trip.
Good and you?
Seek, seek.
Sorry, Mr. President, but there's a problem with that bag.
Hold on, hold on. What's wrong with it? What's wrong?
You see, she's a sniffer dog.
If she gets excited like that, that means there's something in the bag.
There could be some… You know, in the bag.
I mean, like, you know, like, I guess…  What?
They're plushies.  Sorry.
Should I search the bag?
It's the president. What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you guys over here? What's your problem in the West Indies?
Even the dogs are racists, is that it?
Not at all, Mr. President, it's…
Sit. Stop. That's not my France mleh at all.
Not my France mleh. I'm sorry, Mr. President.
These are soft plushies.
Désiré said they're Creole plushies for adults to give away in the 'hood.
Go ahead, Mr. President.  That dog is sniffing plushies.
Thank you, coz. You're a fucking pain.
I have something to share. You have to keep the secret.
What? I'm Turkish.
Just as I suspected. From Izmir?
No, from Bodrum. Ah, all right.
You have to come visit. My whole family's there.
You'll be welcome with open arms.
NEW VIDEO MESSAGE
RESIGN OR THIS GETS OUT