While President Blé and his social policies
seem to be rejected by the majority of French people,
a mob of Frédéric Cognard's supporters have stormed the Élysée
after Cognard turned down the Prime Minister position.
They're endangering our institutions and democracy as we speak.
We still haven't heard from President Blé, who must be feeling threatened.
FRANCE SHAKEN
Over here, Mr. President.  Yeah.
It's here.  Where is it?
It's not here, this one. Oh yeah, that's the one.
Come on, Alice.
You don't know where the bunker is? Yeah, I do.
Yeah!
This place is too spotless. Get this place clean.
Let's stand together. This is our home!
We have rightful ownership of all these things.
It's here! Found it. Go ahead, I'll take care of it.
Ah!  Let's capture them!
We'll keep up with the events throughout the night so you can experience it live
and see these tragic events unfold.
PRESIDENT NOWHERE TO BE FOUND
Where's Blé? Where is he?  Mess up this furniture!
You bastard!
We're going to look for him!
Yeah!
Let's invite him to our home!
REPRESENT
They're out of control. Let's sequester ourselves.
Okay. Very good. We're safe here.  Yeah.
It's okay. It's completely isolated.
What do you mean, "isolated"? I get a bit claustrophobic…
Don't worry, William, there's no problem. I have the situation under control.
I'm gonna contact the outside right away, so they can extract us soon.
It has to happen fast. I can't breathe. Damn it, there's no signal.
Try the landline. No signal? What do you mean, no signal?
It means there's no…
If the signal doesn't get in, the oxygen doesn't get in.
I'm panicking. We're gonna die. We're gonna die!
Calm down.  We're gonna die!
Are you okay? Thanks.
Yeah, I just can't believe what's happening.
Yeah. But it's gonna be fine, don't worry.
We're going to die! I can't breathe!
What can I do to help?
Is it true, what you said earlier?
That you love me?
Stéphane, now isn't the time. Um, well, yes, it is.
If we're gonna die, I'd like to know.
You've just said it's gonna be fine.
Yeah, it's gonna to be fine.
But did you mean it or not?  I'm hungry.
What's that got to do with anything?
Mmhmm.  Fucking hell, Mo.
We have to breathe before we eat.  Get him under control.
Okay, okay, listen up! Guys, please!
You have to calm down.
We're all safe here.
What matters most right now is that we're all together.
We're gonna die, Stéphane! Whoa!
Mr. President?
Perhaps we could have a talk?
Mama!
PRIME MINISTER'S OFFICE
Protesters have stormed the Élysée.
The president is in danger. Let's take action.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Forgive me, General, but I fear this isn't a good idea.
We… We can't fire on demonstrators who are nonviolent and…
And innocent.
Peaceful and innocent? Come on, please, Mr. Andréï.
Yes, General, yes.
We… We are human.
It's not up to us to make these types of decisions.
However,
our president did give the order,
he did,
to fire at the crowd.
He didn't give us the order to fire at the crowd.
I hear you, Andréï.
Can I talk to you for a minute, please?
Yes, I see. Excuse me, General.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
I'm not against low blows, but clean low blows.
This one's nasty.
Mm. Do you have a credit card on you?
Yes.
Well, then, it's about time you go buy yourself a pair of balls.
You understand me?
When you start something,
you have to finish it.
Hmm?
You don't go to the ball
unless you want to dance, right?
So do you want to dance? Or are you out?
Excuse me.
It's Alice.
Hello?  Everything is fine.
The president is safe in the bunker. Oh, my Lord!
Everything's under control.
The president's safe.  Hello? Hello?
Andréï?  Sorry.
I was with General Puch and Jérôme.  Oh yeah? Okay.
Is he with you right now? Yes, he's next to me, I believe.
I'm sure he is. Can I talk to him, Alice, please?
Hello? Andréï? Stéphane.
Man, oh man, how are you?
Listen, you find a way to get us out of here right away.
Don't worry. I'll take care of that.
Every one of our teams have been mobilized.
Don't worry, in an hour, it'll all be resolved. Believe me.
You hear me? Yeah, Andréï. You'd better. Seriously.
The republic won't give way…
…to savagery.
Well, I can tell you that the president is fine.
Hand in hand, Mr. Andréï.
Oh damn, I've got a cramp right here.
I can't breathe in here.
There's no oxygen.
It's totally… It's gotta be airtight.
How much water do we have left? Two bottles.
What? Two bottles?  Two bottles.
We have two bottles left?
That's enough.  I can't calm down.
One bottle for me, that's for sure. My skin gives me a lot of trouble.
It starts with blisters, so I have to drink a lot of water.
We might end up having to drink our own urine.
I saw that in a documentary. Guys who crashed in Colombia.
They started eating each other
That bitch! She's completely crazy!
Look, don't you touch me! Calm down, William.
Go over there. Over there! You don't touch me!
You're crazy! So, what do we do now?
Why are you staring at me?
Maybe those guys have calmed down.  Let's check right now.
We still don't know where the president is,
and the police are having a hard time bringing back order.
One thing is certain, nobody can predict the outcome of this crisis.
No worries. I'm alive and well.
That's Didier!
I had this feeling like we'd forgotten something, you know?
That was Nesrine Slaoui live from the Élysée,
waiting to know more on President Blé's current situation.
Our teams have been mobilized to cover these riots,
and you've guessed it, the epicenter of the insurrection
happens to be located right next to the Élysée.
Lord, Jesus.
If you save my son,
I swear he'll attend Mass on a weekly basis.
Amen.
Don't worry too much.
Your son can withstand anything. Like a rat in a sewer.
…culminated in the assault on the Élysée.
And now, we bring you the latest update that has just come in.
The prime minister will speak soon. Reporting live from Matignon.
My dear fellow citizens.
It is with a heavy heart that I come before you this evening.
STATEMENT FROM PRIME MINISTER
The news coming from the Élysée is concerning.
Our military forces have been mobilized.
That's why I'll let the Chief of Staff talk.
General Puch.
Thank you, Mr. Prime Minister.
Today, at 10:36 p.m.,
President Blé gave me the order to open fire on the peaceful protesters…
What? …at and near the Élysée.
Did you tell him that? I never said that.
This order was obviously unconstitutional
and against all rules of military engagement.
I have thus informed the president of my refusal to carry out his order.
I have sworn to defend my country, not kill my fellow citizens.
The bastard. Prime Minister.
The fucking bastard.
What the…
Damn, bro. Fuck.
Bearing this new information in mind,
and in accordance to all the institutions of the Republic,
we've decided to take action and begin the impeachment process
against President Stéphane Blé…
What? …for high treason.
Stéphane,
it's no longer the prime minister talking to you. It's your friend.
What a bastard.
Let us stop this madness.
IMPEACHMENT OF THE PRESIDENT
Turn yourself in without any resistance.
Let's give back to France its serenity…
…so that it can progress as before.
Long live the Republic.
Long live France.
Holy shit.
A masterpiece. Beautifully done.
It's a masterpiece of a coup. What a delicate, beautiful job.
It's clean, neat, no blunders.
So does it mean… We're fucked.
High treason for us too?
Fuck.  'Cause I didn't do anything wrong.
Hold on. Come on. What we need to do is alert the media.
We, we have to tell them the truth.  Oh? Hey, wake up.
Andréï has a firm grip on the narrative.
We're screwed, all right?
It's over.
Rats deserting a sinking ship.
No, let me explain.
There's no ship anymore. Actually, there never was one.
Or if we were on a ship, it went down, and it's over.
I'm not the kind of guy who's willing to fight arms in hand.
Sorry. We don't even have weapons.
Yeah, yeah, even though I asked for some, right?
Come on. Shall we go now?
Turn yourself in, Mr. President.
Come out and you won't be harmed.
Did he tell us to come out?
Hmm… I just heard "Mr. President."
He's got a stutter.  Who's first? Yeah, go ahead.
You go. No, hold on.
Wait, wait up. What's…
I'm not going. Go ahead and call me. Call me when…
All right, I'm coming. Okay.
Mr. President, I… I'm sorry, if you don't come out now,
we'll have to blow up the doors with explosives.
If I turn myself in, how do I know you won't kill me?
We're the French army, Mr. President. We're fucked…
We're dead. They're gonna kill us.
We're dead. We're not dead at all.
On the contrary… I'm scared right now.
…it's the French Army, so I believe we're fine.
That's my opinion. It's okay.
Mr. President!
If I turn myself in, I want my family spared.
Granted. And my team, also.
Thank you.  Granted. You can trust us.
I don't have a choice.
I'll turn myself in on three. Why three?
I was going to ask the same question.
Mr. President… It's all good.
I'm the one they want.
No, hold on, hold on. Oh man.
Oh, God…
One.
Two.
You know, it's… It's not that I don't trust you, Eric.
But apart from General Puch and yourself,
nobody's heard the president mutter something about firing at the crowd.
Tell me, Thierry.
You want some? No.
Sure? No, thanks.
At the time you submitted your candidacy for Senate president…
Mmhmm?
…I think that I called a few people to support you, didn't I?
Yes, you did. That was very nice of you.
Mm.
And who got you out of nasty trouble when you hired your wife as an assistant
in the administration?
I think it was…
Is it Japanese?
What's Japanese?
Your whiskey. I don't know.
Oh.  So?
No, hold on. It wasn't like that. She did real work. She prepared my notes.
I believe you. Okay.
I believe you because I trust you.
Hmm. And in return,
I would like for you to trust me too.
As president of the Senate, only you can impeach him.
That man is definitely guilty of high treason.
Hmm.
Do you understand?
Mm…
So, Thierry. Can I trust you or not?
Can I trust you?
You can, Prime Minister.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Are you doing okay?
They're negotiating. We think Stéphane will soon come out alive.
Thanks for the update.
Okay, tell Puch to go all out now.
No, we can't just blow up the Élysée's bunker.
I can't believe it. Must I do everything by myself?
Fuck!
Hey, uh, wait for me.
All right.
Come out and you will not be harmed.
So, guys, what's happening?
Can you tell me what you're waiting for?
It's okay, he's about to come out.
"It's okay, he's about to come out."
Have you been sucking on a comb, soldier?
Can't you see he's just buying some time? So blow this door up right now.
Yes, Mr. Prime Minister.
Go, go, go, go!
Why?
Why did you do that?
Lamine, are you insane?
Finally, I can help you out of a jam.
Take these stairs, we'll end up on the street.
Are you crazy? You can't be seen with us.
You just can't, you understand? You sure?
Come on, go. We can handle it, we're good.
Just go now.
Here.
Wait for them, wait for them.
What are you doing? Move!
I'm stuck at the shoulders.  Suck your stomach in!
Get on your side.  Oh, man!
Your ass is right in my face, dude!
I'm mixed CongoleseIvorian, that's why.
The ass has me stranded down there as well.
Squeeze your butt. Give me your arm.  That's repulsive!
I can see your ass.  Give me your hand.
Stéphane, we've got to get out of here.
Mr. President, focus.
Ooh!
Where is he? Wow. Impressive.
Where is he? Pardon?
The president. Where is he?
Yeah, I got that. He's, uh… He's here. I'll find him right away. Hold on.
Stéphane? Hey.
Hello? Mr. President.
Oh, he's gone.
He left. He, uh, might be in London.
I know you so well I could be your dad.
Mmhmm.
You're not a hero.
You're a coward. A little piece of shit.
Oh…
But I know you're not stupid.
Hmm. So what is it that you want?
You want to be the Secretary of the Interior?
The Prime Minister?
Tell me where he is, and I'll give you what you want.
Oh yeah?
I don't want anything, actually.
I don't want anything, because I agree with you.
Stéphane is a guy…
I mean, he's not dumb.
He is. No, he's a dreamer.
No, he's a moron. No, not at all.
He embodies something real.
What?
A sense of hope.
Yeah? That makes you laugh, huh?
Yeah.
Because you don't know what hope is.
I spent an entire life believing in nothing.
And suddenly, I believe in something. In someone, to be accurate.
You know? Yes.
And now, every night, I feel real good about going to bed
with a clear conscience.
And that's awesome.
It's really awesome.
You should try, I'm telling you. I can imagine. I can imagine.
In any case, I can tell you where you're going to sleep tonight.
Well, at my house.
In prison.
Yeah. I'm going to put you in a nice little cell.
We don't have to… I'm gonna put you with the pedophiles.
What? Yes.
You know what they do to pedophiles in the shower room?
Do you know the diameter of your asshole? Beg your pardon?
I'm asking if you know the width of your anus.
I understood the question. I didn't mean for you to repeat it.
So you tell me where he is.
I'll count to three. After that, I'll tase you.
One.
Listen to me.  Where is he? Two.
Soweto. South Africa! Tase this piece of shit.
Give it.
Uh, he could…
He's close to kicking the bucket, even.
Wow, it's already dead. Look.
There's no more juice, which is perfect.
We can leave.
This thing could use some fresh batteries.
I'll change the battery. Go find him now.
I'm on it. Quick, quick, quick!
Doesn't smell like hope, huh, little man?
Smells like shit.
Empower the people!  Empower the people!
Get down. Get down.
There are cops everywhere. What do we do?
We should go hide in the 'hood.
That's a good idea, come on. Let's take the Métro. It's not far.
There are security cameras everywhere in there.
Exactly. Stop it.
Who's ever gotten arrested by a security camera in the Métro?
Lots of guys, actually.
Huh?  That's what it's for.
They can zoom in and everything. You sure?
Yeah.
Really? Okay.
Guys, why don't we go to Corinne's? She can hide us in her village.
How, though? Paris is on lockdown.  Come on, let's cross.
Hey, hey, hey…
Come on, Mo, hide me!
I won't spill the beans on his whereabouts.
Mr. President?
No, no, no, I look a lot like him, but I swear it's not me!
You're really pushing it, man.
I don't have the words…  Sorry, sorry.
Mr. President, we support you. We know the news is fake. It's all good.
Yeah, hop on. We can hide you.
No, no, no, no. Who says you won't report us?
I thought solutions came from below?
Alice?
What's the matter? Come on, you can go now.
No, I have to stay with you and ensure your safety, Mr. President.
My safety. That's a pretty big word, no offense.
Go. It's an order. You can go.
Wow. Okay.
By the way, it's kind of lame to have an air vent
leading straight into the bunker, isn't it?
Yeah, it's true, it's not very smart, not at all, but it's…
Well, it's a French bunker. Can't I stay with you, Mr. President?
No, you can't. Good luck, Alice.
Farewell, Mr. President.
Good luck. No "farewell." That's too dramatic.
["Gasolina (feat. Gambi)" by Hamza playing]
Why are we stopping here?
We live here.
We found the president's phone in a trash can.
In a trash can? Mmhmm.
He could be anywhere by now.
No, I don't think he could. Everyone would recognize him.
I bet he's hiding at home. I don't see anywhere else.
If he went home, he's on our turf.
So get everybody on it.
Any law enforcement officer, drug dealer, or kebab vendor.
Provide a substantial subsidy to anyone who locates him.
General, you're going to put the city on lockdown.
Lock down the whole city. State of emergency.
Nobody comes in, nobody comes out.
A new development in the crisis that is shaking the country.
Prime Minister Eric Andréï has declared a state of emergency in the capital,
which will last until President Blé has been found.
Parisians are thus ordered to stay home until further notice.
There.
Thank you. No, thank you.
We live here thanks to your project.
Your "Living Together" project, Mr. President.
I used to live in a highrise crib.
A what? Highrise crib.
Um, what the hell is that? Lowincome apartment.
Ah. Yes, that's what I said. Yeah.
Now the kids have a lot more room to play, you know?
Hmm. We're mleh.
Here. Thanks. Thanks.
All right, I've got to go to work. Make yourselves at home, okay?
Thank you so much.  Good luck, Mr. President.
Thanks.
So? I talked to my guy. It's taken care of.
All right. Uh…
There's a boat waiting for us in Beauvais. In 24 hours, we're in Abidjan.
Huh?
A boat? Yeah.
In Beauvais? Sorry, I couldn't find one any closer.
So it's in Beauvais. You sure?
Well, I looked. I couldn't find one.
I can't accept your stupidity anymore.
Huh? There's no sea in Beauvais.
What? Yeah, Mo, everyone knows that.
Hold on, should we be focusing on this little detail?
Come on. When, then if not now? Can't we talk about that later?
Don't we have more pressing matters?
Also, my guy wants to be paid up front, so deal with it.
Oh man.
Are you okay?
I truly apologize.
When I married you, all I wanted was a dramafree life.
And now we're fugitives.
Listen, when I married you, I knew it was gonna be a mess.
I signed up for it.
You didn't sign up for this.
But I signed up.  Come check this out!
Do you realize? He wanted to fire at peaceful protesters.
I'm sure if you spend that much time supporting jihadists,
you wind up using their methods.
Huh? Jihadists? Why not terrorists? I call for Stéphane Blé's impeachment.
And I'm asking for new presidential elections,
so France and the French people can return to a peaceful and safe state.
Stéphane Blé is gullible. He's a coward. And he's weak, of course.
She's exaggerating a little. Also, misogynistic.
It's too much.  Don't do this.
He would've never given the order to fire at the crowd.
The president remains nowhere to be found, and civil society has rallied up.
Supermarket cashiers,
delivery drivers, taxi drivers, maintenance staff,
everyone threatens to block the country if Stéphane Blé is impeached.
You see? France isn't against you.
…spontaneous protests are taking place in support of the president.
Can we send a message directly on the Élysée's account?
Mmhmm. All right, go ahead and film me, please.
Dear French citizens,
this is Stéphane Blé speaking, your president.
Let me be clear with you.
I never ordered to open fire on the crowd.
Andréï is portraying me as a scumbag. I'll prove to you that I'm innocent.
And for that, I'll need everyone.
You, me, him, her, and even they too.
Just keep going.
I am moving on.
I need for everyone to rise up and root for me.
They wanna destroy me.
Stéphane is broadcasting a live message. We found the signal.
He's in an apartment five minutes away. Okay, perfect.
Send in special forces, SWAT teams, a few fighter jets if we have to.
If he must fall, he will fall.
Mmhmm.
That way, he'll get to join his 70 virgins ahead of schedule.
Funny, but I don't think he's a Muslim. What would he be, then?
An animist?
Huh?  An animist.
What are the animists promised?
Must be cars.
Cars. Trinkets, maybe. Anyway, who gives a fuck?
Go for it. Get out.
What are animists promised?
Dear French citizens.
All Andréï wants is to set us against each other.
Police! Give yourself up!
But we're better than that.
Right now, it's not about me as a person.
We don't care about me. You have elected me.
Hands in the air!  Right now…
Ah!
…it's your choice that's being stolen.
I've decided to protect my loved ones.
They shouldn't be the ones paying for this.
What is she doing? Marion, Marion, stop it. We have to go.
But I'm gonna fight.
Because our democracy is sick, and it's up to us to take good care of it.
No one else.
So we won't go down without a fight.
We won't give up,
just like the Doc Gynéco song, for those who remember.
I truly encourage everyone to join together.
Let's restore the dignity of our nation, France.
This is why I urge all French citizens to join me in the fight.
People from cities, the countryside, everywhere.
Those who work. Those who are unemployed.
People of all ethnicities, of all sexualities.
Straight, bi, gays, asexuals, those who never do it.
Alone, we are powerless. But together, we are unbeatable.
Long live France. Long live the resistance mleh.
No two ways about it. I'll be back.
All together. All together. Yeah. Yeah.
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Screaming, "One day, one day" ♪
♪ Hey, hey, one day ♪
♪ "I will be the president" ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪