I don't think he likes applesauce.
I don't give a fuck. You feed your hostage.
Do you know the Geneva Convention? Hold on, he's not my hostage.
He's not my hostage. Who brought him here? He's your hostage.
But I…
Why is he taking so long, for fuck's sake?
Honestly, it wasn't a good idea to call him.
Who did you want us to call? Yasmine? She'd have killed us.
You didn't give me a choice.
He's the only one who can get us out of this mess.
So, what's the minor issue you've got?
What the fuck is this, guys? What are you doing? Who is this?
That's the Norwegian ambassador. Huh? What?
I swear, my heart was in the right place.
It's all right. Mo gave him a little roughing up, nothing too serious.
Roughing up? Look, he's fine.
Yeah, but honestly, he looks like a Nazi.
Come on, dude, you need to stop thinking that all blonds are Nazis.
There were Nazis with brown hair, with red hair.
There were fat Nazis, skinny Nazis, women Nazis.
It's a super inclusive group, FYI. Come on.
Okay.
Fuck, I thought this was a minor issue, like you two groped an assistant.
But this is some major shit right here.
That's fucked up.  What made you do this?
We need your help. That's why we called.
If you get us out of this, I'll reinstate you on the team.
Shut up.
I swear.
Are you serious? Tell the truth.  Yeah. I swear.
At the Élysée. With a driver, everything.
Oh, fuck, man. That's awesome.
Well, don't worry. We're gonna figure this out. Hmm…
Did he recognize you guys? Did he see you?
No, no. Okay. All right.
Take a look. Look.
When we took off his blindfold, we put on our masks.
Yeah. So he fucking saw you guys.
I told you these weren't the right ones!
Some of them are opaque, so you can't see the face!
Well, uh, there's only one solution, guys.
Good thing I came with a utility vehicle.
I can park with the trunk facing the Élysée,
open the the back doors, you put him in there,
and we bury him in the forest.
I like it. That's a great plan.
You can't be fucking for real. What's up, man?
I'm not killing anybody. That's not my style.
You won't kill him. I will. No.
He committed suicide. He was depressed.
You're full of it! I won't kill anyone. The Élysée has a number of body counts.
Mitterrand with Coluche.
Dalida, Balavoine, "L'Aziza."  Claude François!
Him too? Of course. It was jumper cables.
Not a hairdryer.
What's that?
Is that his…
You didn't turn off his phone? You didn't turn off his phone?
It was in a foreign language.
Fuck this shit, man. It's just getting worse and worse.
It's okay, it's okay. This is fucked up.
It's all right. What are you doing?
Shush. I'm just…
Fuck this shit.
Easy. Uh…
Excuse me, I'm just going to take the phone that's ringing, don't worry.
What are you doing? Don't answer. Stop it!
Yes?
I… I love you.
I'm going to eat.
Thanks. Thank you.
It was the Norwegian Embassy.
The Norwegian Embassy? You didn't turn off his phone.
They traced it. They know he's at the Élysée.
Goddamn it.  We're busted.
What the fuck should we do now?
Okay, first, you shut your mouth. Both of you, shut up.
Second…
don't talk about this to anyone.
For sure.
Thirdly, I'll go talk to the Norwegians, try to calm them down.
Thanks. I would have been bummed out to lose the job because of his bullshit!
Let me explain. No matter what, you're both losing your jobs.
That's for sure. What?
The question is, how long will you serve in prison?
Huh? That's inevitable.
I predict 20 years for you, man. What?
Yeah, you kind of look like a thug, makes people want to…
You, since you're not that buff physically,
they're gonna pity you and give you five years.
Oh man. Five minimum.
Two suspended and three Hopefully. That's a real downer.
We'll hope for the best. Inshallah.
Inshallah.
All right.
I'm going to put the phone back on the box, Mr. Norwegian.
Stéphane.
REPRESENT
Yeah.
Do you have a minute? I want to talk to you about something real quick.
I have a cabinet meeting, but go ahead. No problem.
All right.
I have an idea for a tax. Ah, it's about work?
Of course it's about work.
Ah. My idea is the Béké tax.
Béké?
Yeah. The Békés. The white landowners in the Antilles.
Oh yeah.
When slavery was abolished, the French government bought their slaves.
I don't know if you realize how much they make.
They have distilleries, supermarkets and stuff. It's nuts.
So what we're gonna do is impose a tax,
then our money is returned and slave descendants are compensated.
Awesome idea. You think so?
Great idea. I'm glad you like it.
I'd even add something too.
As the first Black president of France, I'd have to go further.
I must withdraw French troops from Africa.
Yup. Yeah.
Yup to all that. This is the end of colonialism.
You got it. Excellent job. I'm impressed.
And if you want, tonight we could talk about it oneonone?
No.  Mr. President, can I talk to you?
I'd like you to meet Aimé.
Who's Aimé?
He will be your wife's bodyguard from now on.
What?
Why? I don't understand. I mean…
How come you're making me do this?
You're not listening. I don't want it.
I said I didn't want a bodyguard. Why would I need one?
Honey, we still haven't found all the terrorists,
and I don't want anything to happen to you.
Have him come in.
God's sake. Here's Aimé.
Mr. President.
Morning.
You know, she's capable of defending herself on her own.
She's really strong…
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Blé. At your service.
Come on.
What's the deal with Marion's bodyguard?
Aimé?
He's good, huh? But…
You could have found someone who was less…
I mean, more normal, you know? What do you mean, "normal"?
Oh, don't even worry. He's 100% gay.
Are you sure? Certain.
I've seen it with my own eyes, so…
Any news from William? William? The problem is, uh…
William?
No, I didn't say "William." I said "Wilhelm."
Yeah.
Who's that?
He's a young Kabyle singer we're gonna to invite to the Élysée for Music Day.
Oh yeah? He's a really great singer.
What does he sing?
Um…
♪ Ooh ♪ ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
Then the beat goes like this and…
♪ Doo, doo, doo, doo, yeah ♪
You've fucked up. No!
No.  Swear.
Islam doesn't allow me to swear.
Yeah. You're not even a Muslim.
It's a religion which I respect very much, that's why.
Me too.
Listen to me carefully, both of you. If I find out that you've fucked up…
Everyone expects us to fuck up.
We have to be beyond reproach until the legislative elections.
Isn't it better to be beyond reproach after the elections?
Mostly before.
Calm down. I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding either, Yasmine. Calm down.
Yeah, calm down. Seriously. Calm down.
Man!  Unbelievable.
The President of the French Republic.
Salaam, shalom. Hello, everyone.
Hi. Good morning, Mr. President.
Patriarchal tardiness. Great start.
Awesome. Thanks.
Hello.  Hello.
Hello.
Antoine Journo, Mr. President.
Our Minister of Sports.
Like parasports, or…
No, just sports.
Okay.
Uh. So, Corinne, I'm telling it to you straight.
First I'll implement the "Eat well, for free" bill,
then we can implement your bills.
If I may, Mr. President, uh, your bill is somewhat out of budget.
So if I have to pick, I pick the environmental transition.
You can't do this to me. You told me it was within our budget.
No. She's the one who told you that.
Not me.
When I said within our budget,
it was, uh, with a growth projection of 3.2%.
And right now, we're at 1.8%, so…
I don't care about the 1.8%.
I made a promise, and I intend to follow through
and implement this bill.
So let's fucking find the funds.
We could abolish military nuclear spending.
This is Clément Arenou, our secretary of defense.
Just like the Bastille Day parade.
It's pointless.
Yeah, I'm totally with you on that one.
I also think we should abolish the CFA franc.
And let's pull out all those French troops from Africa.
It would be my pleasure.
I would disband the entire military if I could.
Excellent. We should terminate military nuclear spending first,
then civilian nuclear power while we're at it because…
Whoa, whoa.
I completely agree with the views expressed by everyone, right?
We have a lot to do in the social realm, for the environment,
education, justice, et cetera.
But after the legislative elections.
Because if we lose them, we won't do anything at all.
So until then, sorry, but we're gonna make symbolic changes, and cheap changes.
Come on, we can't just focus on the legislative elections.
We have to get to work. It's important, in my opinion.
You don't care, since you always lose elections.
Oh wow. Okay, then.
You all right? Hello.
What's this guy doing?  Who's this?
I got this.
Stéphane?
Uh, actually, he's here to help me handle a case in the West Indies.
What case?
Sorry. Excuse me, but the thing on your…
Sorry.
Why does she have a cauliflower on her head?
Am I the only one seeing this?
It's a Nigerian gele, not cauliflower.
All right. Cultural appropriation. That's awesome.
No, it's not cultural appropriation.
It's the mark of support for the fight of women who…
Hey, you!
Yeah? Not interested in the fate of women?
Yeah, bigtime. Yes.
Uh, so I talked to the Norwegians. They sent him back to Norway.
It's all good. Uh, they won't say anything.
But in order to avoid a diplomatic incident,
Norway demands that you meet with the queen.
Do I have to? If you don't, you'll be locked up, man.
So I guess there's no other way. Okay.
Sorry. Uh, I'm sorry, ladies and gentlemen.
Sorry.
Really.  What are you doing?
We have a press conference in ten minutes.
Well, tell them we're inviting the Queen of Norway.
Exactly. The Queen of Norway? Why?
Have you lost it? Norway is a fossil fuel heaven.
And don't get me started on the slaughter of whales in Greenland.
And why do you think we're inviting her? Precisely to address all these concerns.
Exactly. Yeah.
Oh, the slaughter? Show her pictures. I have some on me.
I'll give them to you. I always have these pictures on me.
I know. I have all the photos… No, wait. Mine are really illuminating.
No, that's my notebook. Hold on, guys.
Let's go. My menstrual cup.
Hold on, hold on, that's…  Where
What's that?
My menstrual cup.
To gather menstrual blood during my period.
It's 100% more ecological than tampons.
I don't understand, where do you put that? Do you put that in your…
You think I put it where?
It's in my bag because I'm not on my period, otherwise, sure.
She still has her period.  Yes!
Absolutely, I still have mine.
Like 15 million French women, seven million have painful periods.
Do you think that's fair?
To have your period?
No. Painful periods.
Do you think it's right to go to work when you're in pain in a country like France?
No! Well…
It shouldn't be that way, so I'd like to talk about menstrual leave.
What do you think? That's bold.
Yes, I agree. Yeah. Of course, women agree.
What do men think?  Yes.
What do we think? Yes? Yeah.
There.
So let's put the menstrual leave on the agenda the next meeting, thanks.
So, Mr. Cognard, what do you think
of the first turmoil in the BléDouanier administration?
FAR RIGHT SOON IN POWER
According to reports, it's quite shaky right now.
Of course it is, obviously. A thug and a lunatic wearing a hijab.
A hijab! Dear Lord.
At the higher reaches of the government. Nothing surprising there.
Anyway, all this government wants is that our kids change sex or to become imams.
Wait a minute, that's one big shortcut there.
Not at all. Not at all.
What do you think he means with this "France mleh"?
My God. It means France halal, pretty much.
And while real French people go hungry, what do they do?
They invite a queen.
But I have a message for them.
The legislative elections are coming up,
and the honkies are gonna fuck you over real deep.
Oh my God. What a statement. Well, you are determined.
So, real deep, I don't know, but in the electoral campaign,
there seems to be an interesting dynamic at play.
And if you win with the alliance of the rightwing and the far right,
you have the potential to gain seats in the assembly.
About time. About time. A kick in the balls by the blue boots.
You mean just the one ball. The ball.
This whole Queen of Norway thing is a disaster.
We've lost four points in two hours.
We should go back to lowincome neighborhoods, your base,
and get young and old people to vote.
Good morning.
Sorry, do you know why I'm laughing? Because I see someone who is panicking.
Stop panicking. Listen and learn.
We're going to light a counterfire,
to distract the attention and change the narrative.
And it'll be solved. I'm telling you, it'll be resolved.
Stop freaking out. Change the narrative?
Without "Eat well, for free," we're screwed.
"Change the narrative."
No, I think we have to do a symbolic gesture,
like change the name of the Place Charles de Gaulle.
Wow! Ah!
My ears hurt.
Are you listening to yourself? It makes no sense.
In France, there are things you can't touch.
There are some constants. You can never touch de Gaulle.
Hold on, guys, I don't want symbolic gestures, all right?
I want to change French people's lives concretely.
That's what I want. And for cheap.
For cheap, yeah, I guess.
Yeah, that was the idea originally, wasn't it?
So in that case… Mr. President.
'Sup, Mr. Alain Feuillet?
I'm sorry to disturb you, but you requested that I notify you
if any complications arise with Lamine.
And there's a big problem with Lamine.
Oh, Black people. It's always the same thing.
You want to help, and they get you in trouble.
We don't even know what the problem is. It's always the same.
He's very tardy. Oh yeah, always the same.
He's not here now. You're right. It's always the same.
It's just nuts, the whole…
…CPT thing.
They can't be on time. I'm mixed race, so I'm half on time, but…
What are we eating for lunch? What?
Tournedos Rossini. Yes! All right. That works.
Bro, are you for real?
You know what will happen if you don't finish your community service hours?
Of course I know. Do you think I'm happy about it?
The chef says you're late every morning.
Am I late to work? It's easy for you. You live here.
I don't see the point.
Every day, I have a twohour commute back and forth.
Metro 11's being renovated. The commuter rail sucks.
I swear, Stéphane, it's not that I don't want to,
but that's a twohour commute every day.
Two hours.
This whole equalityofopportunity thing or whatever is bullshit.
Maybe we could have him live here.
Hello? Yasmine?
Yeah, call the press back. I have something to say.
Not in the Élysée.
Directly in the 'hood. You already know.
Sorry, but if we do that, it's political suicide.
The opposition will be on our asses.
Not at all. I checked. We'll be able to pass it as an ordinance.
It's not that expensive, and it's super popular.
Not that expensive? It's not.
French taxpayers are paying… Mr. President.
Uh, it's really too risky.
You have to keep it short with the terrorist threat against you.
Quickly.
What? What did she say? What are you doing?
It's the Legion of Honor necklace. We're not at a WuTang concert.
Take this off. I want to honor the people.
Take it off, please. And the people, that's us.
Today, I'm here to talk about housing. What do you see here?
Go back to the Congo!
Thank you, sir.
I'm certain that on this street,
there are dozens and dozens of unoccupied apartments.
It's the same all over France.
Just in Paris, over 100,000 apartments are empty.
And we know that every morning,
some people spend one to two hours in public transportation,
to come to work.
Whereas right next door to their job,
there are unoccupied apartments due to speculation.
You think that's okay? I personally don't.
So from tomorrow onwards,
I will be having conversations with mayors,
unions, and local organizations
so that people who need to, can live closer to their work.
That's also the France mleh.
And if the negotiations don't work, will you requisition them?
Well, no. Of course we won't.
Yeah, if we have to, I wouldn't mind. No.
That's communism if you do that.
Not at all, sir. It's called living together.
It's also communism a little bit. A little bit of communism.
I'll speak my mind, if that's okay with you.
With your idea of living together,
you're wide off the mark.
Jeanette, you've got a nerve to tell me that,
given you're always crashing at my place at the Élysée.
This isn't your place here, son. It's the house of the people.
Amen. What is he doing standing over there?
Come eat with us, come on.
Thank you, ma'am. I've already eaten.
Ha! "Ma'am"?
You can call me auntie, you know.
I prefer to call you "ma'am." Ah, jeez.
I like your "living together" idea. I think it's a good one.
I like it.
Thanks.
It's a good idea, yes.
But an enemy is going to stand in your way.
Mmhmm. Yeah, I know.
The Homeowners Union, all that.
No.
Belzebuth.
Mmhmm.
Every time someone wants to do something good,
the devil makes sure it won't happen.
But you will always be protected by the Lord, my son.
Amen. Say "amen." Amen.
Mm… Amen.
Logically, every Black person should support you,
but we don't stick together.
That's why white people colonized us. No, come on Jeanette, you can't say that.
Of course I can say it.
Africa is where it's at right now because of Black people themselves.
We have to stop saying it's white people's fault.
No, no, Jeanette, that's enough. What? What will you do to me?
Aren't you offended by what she's saying? Huh?
All right, well, I have work to do, so…
No, stay here. Come on.
Wait, come on  See you.
Meet you in the bedroom?  I don't think so.
Mm!
Hmm! That young woman is impolite.
Did you see that?  I don't understand.
What are you playing at?
I'm trying to make up with her, and you're obstructing my efforts.
Those girls from Zaire… She's not from Zaire, she's from Senegal.
…they're the worst breed.
On principle, we have nothing against "living together," Mr. President.
But the owners I represent had to borrow money
to pay for those apartments.
They have mortgages to reimburse. They'd go broke.
Perhaps we might offer them a small tax rebate?
Or a big tax allowance would work?
She's messing with you. Of course I'm messing with you.
I mean, think about it for a second. This is what will happen.
We're going to put the public interest ahead of your bourgeois selfinterest.
Otherwise, we're going to requisition all empty apartments.
And we'll do it, that clear? Wait. Come on, Corinne.
Just calm down.
Just please, calm
That thing really suits you.
For real.  Oh thanks.
It's out of solidarity for my sisters going through chemotherapy.
What, do you find cancer funny?
Absolutely not. Cancer is the worst.
And multiple sclerosis makes you laugh?
No, no, it doesn't make me laugh.
But I have to admit some diseases are funny. I'm being honest.
But we're not here to talk about funny diseases, all right?
We're here to talk about "living together."
What can be done to help poor people live in highrent areas. Huh?
That's all I want.
Couldn't we work hand in hand for once, together,
in the best interest of the public?
And what will you cover?
Huh?  Basically, you're imposing a policy
that will cost the government nothing
but put thousands in a shitty situation, and you want our solidarity?
Hold on, what you're doing, sir, is oversimplifying my words.
But yeah, it's true, that's what I'm asking, pretty much.
Well, no, thanks.
I'm sorry, but we must prioritize our interests.
Believe me, all French people do as well. No.
Wait, please, why don't we give this a try on a smaller scale?
Perhaps somewhere near the Élysée, in Paris, or, uh…
Mr. Mayor?
Cousin, cut it out.
You and me, we understand each other, don't we?
Do you get me?
Solidarity, sticking together. Black love.
But, Mr. President, have you lost your mind?
I shouldn't have said that. I'm sorry.
But I want so much. I'm sorry.
Let's be practical. What do you need?
What is it you need?
More public day cares in Paris? More nursing homes?
No, I don't see why my voters should go through this, that's all.
Hold on, Mr. Mayor of Paris.
Don't you want to make history?
Right? To be the first mayor of a large city
to test this social, historical policy.
In London, in Madrid, in New York, nobody else has done this feat.
Do you realize the impact it'll have? The glory?
History books will talk about you.
Women will come ringing at your door, maybe, I don't know,
to have sex with you, I guess.
I'll think about it.
All right. That's cool. So I suggest we try this at the Élysée.
Let's have a garden party with both rich and poor people.
White people, Black people, Jews, Asians, Muslims.
Let's have a blast proving that living together is totally doable.
There, that's what my next five years will be about.
It'll be all about solidarity amongst all French people,
to keep France as we love it.
To make it mleh.
Whoo!
Whoohoo!  Yes!
Today, I also would like to thank my lovely spouse, Marion,
with whom I have gone through so much.
But we've stayed super close anyway.
Marion, you're a heck of a woman,
and I should also say that you're pretty mleh.
Congrats!
Bravo!
Thanks. Thank you all.
Aren't I mleh?
That's our son.
Here, this is a summary of drilling in the Northern Sea and whale fishing.
What, aren't you meeting with the Queen of Norway?
Yeah.
You're lying to me, aren't you?
Okay, here's the truth.
There's another reason. We have another issue.
IKEA packages never have the right number of screws,
and French people are fed up, man.
Isn't it… Excuse me, but IKEA's Swedish.
Right? Of course. It's Swedish.
Exactly. That's the problem.  Mmhmm.
French people should know that.
Yeah.
You need to come clean.
What?  You're lying to me.
What are you saying? You're something.  I am.
Come on, can't you have a good time sometimes?
Who says you can't enjoy yourself? Just have fun. Be like Marion.
Oh yeah, she's having fun. She's definitely enjoying herself.
Oh. I'm not worried at all. He's with the rainbow team.
No, he's not. He's had flings with three women at the Élysée.
They were all consensual, I checked.
But he's hot to trot.
You mean he isn't gay?
Why would he be gay?
Why did he come wearing a pink shirt to his interview if he isn't gay?
I don't see your point.
Claude! Claude, help! What the fuck? Uncle!
Claude! Help! Please help me!
Claude!  Dad?
Stand aside, please. Make room, ma'am.
Sir? Stay with us, sir. Dad? Dad?
That's my father. Sir, stay with me.
Can he hear me? I'm gonna give him mouthtomouth.
Not a man. Damn it.
Please, not a man.
Not a man. What is he saying?
It's because, you're Would you have a female colleague on hand?
No, I don't have a female colleague.
I'll give him mouthtomouth. Give him some space, please.
I'll never get over it if a man puts his mouth on my mouth.
Oh my God. That's nonsense.
Don't worry, he's straight. You're straight, aren't you?
Dad! Dad!
I don't feel a pulse. We have to resuscitate him. Oxygen!
Stop with your African crap! You're gonna die!
We all agree, he's dying of homophobia, am I right?
Dad, I beg you! I mean, he's homophobic and…
Please, ladies and gentlemen, do not touch the buffet anymore.
Step back!
Did he eat something?
He only drank champagne.
Mr. President, I think he's been poisoned.
Have you had any champagne?
How are you feeling?
You're dizzy, aren't you?
Excuse me. Yeah, my bad, my bad. Sorry.
So good. Holy shit!
I had some too.
Ma'am! Ma'am, I've had some too. Sorry, I've had some.
Stéphane?
Stéphane!
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Screaming, "One day, one day" ♪
♪ Hey, hey, one day ♪
♪ "I will be the president" ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪