A NETFLIX SERIES
AMBULANCE
Come on. Stay with us.
Stay with us. Stay with us. Is he gonna make it?
Yeah. But, uh, please don't press…. He's bleeding out.
Hey, fucking hurry up! Shit!
Oh, shit. This is my fault. Shit. I'm sorry.
What? All right, I don't understand.
He's trying to talk. Can you take this off?
Huh?  My nuts!
Your nuts? Oh, right. Fuck.
HOSPITAL
All right, friends.  Well?
The operation went well.
It was great. Great.
He's going to make it.
Longterm effects could happen, because… What else do you people need?
A signed letter? Huh?
"Yo, it's us, the Freemasons. We shot Stéphane Blé!"
Yeah, he's right!
Oh, no, man. No, shut your holes, you two. But they're both onto something, William.
Because coming to Corrèze without any kind of preparation
is completely stupid, huh?
Hey, it's Corrèze, all right?
It's not like it's Right. Right.
I mean, the sponsors, now this. What about the sponsors?
Uh, the sponsors are… It's nothing. Let's talk.
You wanna speak, we'll speak. Yes.
Just us two. There's no reason to cause a scene in front of… the team.
But they can't know? Know what?
Know that I checked three different times, and all our sponsorships are rightwing?
And I was told you didn't want any extra security for this visit.
You're out to get Stéphane.
Listen to me. This is what happens in politics.
You might have a future if you learn from me now. I'm a pro.
Oh, no, no. No, thanks.
What do you mean? Keep your offer of help.
Mrs. Blé? Mrs. Blé?
Please, make room.  Any news about Stéphane?
Please, please. Can you step back?
Do you believe the farright theory?
Sir, please, just wait.
Today, a great blow was just struck at the core of democracy.
As you know, Stéphane Blé is an adversary,
but today,
I'm here to visit a friend and a brother.
A brother, which is why I went right away to get his mother and wife,
so they can be with him too.
What are your thoughts  Thank you.
You were his protector! What did you do? Where is he?
Stéphane's all right? Go on, you can tell us.
He will recover. Oh.
However, he took a bullet to the nuts.
To the… What?
To the testicles.
Oh, fuck. They both weren't hit. It's just the one.
A bullet tore open the testicle a bit.
They're sewing him back up now. They're professionals, so, uh…
Marion, it's okay. It's all right.
And, uh, unfortunately, we're not completely sure about the…
Yeah, that…  What?
Well, he'll be left as…
You know, as a…
He'll be a DJ? What?
I'm not following. No, obviously not. He'll…
His… Ah.
Psst. Lose the arm. But why would they…
Because you're… No! That there are lasting effects.
Ah! Lasting. That's "lasting effects"?
Well, yeah.  Shh.
That's absurd.
The department head is a man I know personally.
He'll get the best treatment. Trust me, he will.
Shall we? Thank you.
I bless you…
…with the blood of our lord Jesus.
I pray to those who chain their foes.
In the powerful blood of Jesus. Hey, hey!
Say "amen"! Mom!
Amen! Amen. Amen.
God bless and protect my son.  Amen.
Why'd you do this to us? Huh?
Hmm. Excuse me.
Hello, Stéphane. Let's go, Simone.
Let's let them talk. Let's let them talk.
God, protect my son. That's good.
Amen!
You scared us a bit, Stéphane, you know?
I want you to know, I will do my utmost
to make sure this crime doesn't go unpunished.
Your sacrifice will not be in vain.
Anyway, you're alive, thank God!
And your testicle is saved.
If the testicle's still here, it seems it's all thanks to you.
You, who work in the shadows, who, despite derision, fatigue,
and, uh, more cutbacks to your budgets,
continue to give your lives in order to save the lives of others.
So I will say this to you directly. Bravo to you.
You're the last rampart against the barbarity of men.
No, no. You're the ones who deserve the applause here.
You fucking bastard.
I think my friend is speaking to me.
What is it?  You fucking bastard.
Yes, of course, they can bring you custard, my friend.
Whatever you want. Mmhmm.  I'll fuck your mom.
I'll fuck your mom.
Ah, he's desperate for his mother. Let's just leave him to rest.
All right, I
Oh, dear. The pain is too great.
Let's go, let's go. We shouldn't stay. Oh, dear.
I'll be around, Stéphane. Stay strong, my brother.
Ah. He's a fighter, our Stéphane, huh?
Yes? You went a little overboard here.
Yeah, I said to hit him hard, true, but not like this.
Yeah, but now we're… we're all set.
Yeah, your perspective is right. Okay.
Still, I've got bad news.
Um. You won't be able to join my team. I can't take you now, you understand?
It might look opportunistic. It's a bad look.
Excuse me? You must see, given this situation
But I Why? I'm not There's no
He had an accident. Big whoop. I mean, II…
It's not really ju likelike I'm switching sides.
You know, I'm joining a campaign that'sthat's successful.
And you And you have to No, I don't, man.
Please, please, please, don't do this. Please, don't.
Unbelievable. You're You're pathetic.
It's Huh?
That moron and you are a great match.
Is that right? Yeah, that's right.
His ball's gone, and you never had any.
Yeah, well, you know what?
In terms of nuts…
you, my friend…
Hmm? I'll tell you what…
What? Well, let me finish.
What? Nothing. You know that, man.
You It's just Look at you.
Yeah, yeah. Look at you, look at me.
France Info,
and we're here with an update on candidate Stéphane Blé,
whose life is no longer in any danger.
Aside from his right testicle,
there were no other injuries to vital organs,
caused by this radicalized extremist, who, and I quote here,
was "sick of having these Blacks busting his balls
in his beautiful Corrèze."
You're a very fortunate man, Mr. Blé.
Five millimeters away from becoming Mrs. Blé.
I'm not laughing. Ah, you just can't make jokes.
I have to donate sperm in a little while. Is that doable?
Could be, but until then, you have to rest,
as a pellet may move and IVF will be futile.
All right. Have a nice day, everyone.
Uh, well, we're doing pretty well, aren't we?
Right?
I've been thinking, and, uh…
I could be the donor in his place. Oh, shut up. Seriously, Mo.
No, but it's pretty easy. It's just Just stop it!
Oh, no. Hey, Mo, I'm fasting today. Why are you doing this to me right now?
I'm saying, I can do it myself.  Don't touch yourself.
Stop looking at me. I'll stop my campaign.
What's that? I'll stop my campaign.
Could you all step out? No, that's not possible.
Stéphane Can you leave? I need to talk to Marion.
Please, just think about it.
He'sHe's clearly in shock. Okay?
We'll talk later. We'll talk, Stéphane. All right.
We'll talk.  Why won't they use me?
Because then, biologically, the child wouldn't be Stéphane's.
We're both African.
You're sure?
Certain.
And since I know it's gonna be a girl,
I'm sure that our Mariam will end up president of the Republic.
Christiane, we decided.
Why would I give my daughter a crazy old lady name like that?
What's up with that? Taubira, bish.
Christiane Taubira. Are you kidding me?
Oh, yeah, that's right. My bad.
Etienne, how are you?  Fine. How's Blé?
Uh, well, listen… Pfft.
He's fine. Yes.  That's good.
Yes, of course, it's good. Wow.
So, I was thinking, I'm available now. Mmhmm. Right.
Uh, maybe you guys have a role for me? You know, special tasks or…
Oh, no, no, no.  Huh?
That's impossible. It'd be opportunistic.
Okay, that's fine, man. Well, okay.
Good luck. Take care. Thanks anyway.
Fuck me.
Three days from the first round of votes in the presidential election.
Rightwing candidate Durandeau is still lagging behind.
He's been overtaken by the farright candidate Fred Cognard.
And Corinne Douanier is also struggling as the deadline approaches.
But with Stéphane Blé's campaign at an abrupt end,
Éric Andréï has really taken off,
and is now showing at 29 percent, topping the polls.
Hey, Stéph, how are you? What's up, girlfriends?
I'll be of age in five years. Campaign again, I'll vote for you.
Hey, power to you. Power. Thanks, girls. Thank you.
For real, I feel kinda bad for him.
Well, we've got good news, Mr. Blé.
All the pellets have fallen to the bottom of the scrotum.
We can proceed with the sample. Wait, um, I've got a question.
Won't it be kind of painful if I start tugging on myself?
With my injury and all. No.
No, but because of the buckshot, it could cause tinkling sounds.
And I think if you try to follow a rhythm, you could do "Jingle Bells."
Of course not. Fill to the mark. You remembered the three abstinence days?
Yeah, we abstained. Ah.
Yeah, for real.
I mean, you wouldn't
You finished? You finished?
It's just that Because of my injury.
So the rhythm, the pace… Uhhuh.
…it's all just a little mismatched.
But when things are normal, I mean, then it's great.
Really, I'm not trying to brag.
No. But it really is. It's…
This thing, it's…
Yes? Hmm?
It's? Uh, nothing.
Good.
Well, you can follow me, ma'am.
What are you doing, Mr. Blé?
Well, you set down the little cup.
There's a special room for that. Please. A nurse will take you.
Oh, okay. All right. Not in my office. Of course not.
All right.
You've got…
the magazines right over here.
And videos… here.
And if there's something else you need, I'm right outside, just give me a call.
No, no, it's fine, yeah. The magazines and the TV are good enough, thanks.
Have a nice day.
Whoa!
Bravo!
Andréï for president! Andréï for president!
Andréï for president! Andréï…
Since the assassination attempt on Stéphane Blé,
the campaign has resumed its course.
One week from the vote,
it's likely the second round will be Andréï and Cognard.
Today, the subject of colonization became the hot topic,
on the 60th anniversary of the truce in Algeria.
Both candidates had their reactions.
At some point, we have to stop being made to feel guilty over colonization.
The real colonization is the one the French are experiencing every day.
Hijabs in schools, halal butcher shops…
With the Fatimas, the Mohammeds.
This colonization, once I'm elected to lead,
it'll be over.
Everyone on a charter, on a flight, straight to the Casbah. Hmm?
Can we change the channel?
Mr. Andréï, your reaction to this?
There's a report on ants that I've been waiting to see now.
So?
Ah, yes, colonization.
It's a topic we must approach with a lot of responsibility.
In many ways, we are unjust.
But may we not consider that…
that colonization has also had some benefits?
Ugh.  …regarding hygiene, uh, or forks.
Whether it's transport, the railway…  Oh, man.
…between Djibouti and Addis Ababa.
That's huge. And bridges. Right? All Africans love bridges.
So, you see, colonization, sure.
We also need to look beyond that and tell ourselves….
♪ Back to the future… future… ♪
STÉPHANE BLÉ HE'S GOT NO BALLS
That's exactly it, man. That's what I keep trying to tell him.
Shit.  What are you guys doing here?
Oh, Mr. President. Come on, chill. Have a seat.
Guys, it's late. Get home!
I'm taking you guys home. Let's go.
No. Mom left the keys in the door. I can't. You know what she's like.
Let's go. I'll get her to answer Hey!
Don't pretend you're my dad, Stéphane! Just stop acting like my dad, all right?
You've got Marion. You're gonna have a family.
That's great for you!
Me, I'm making it on my own. But, sure, I'm all right.
What do you mean? I'm here. I'm not letting you down.
Come on, level with me. You quit your campaign?
Of course you're letting us down. You just quit on us!
That's the thing!
Now you're out, we're supposed to vote for who, huh?
Who you voting for, Stéphane? Voting for what?
The fascist or the bully?
Use your head for once!
Just use your head, for fuck's sake!
You get people's hopes up, then leave 'em in shit.
That's easy, huh? That shit is so easy!
A FRANCE FOR ALL REAL SOLUTIONS COME FROM BELOW
What's up with you?
I'm restarting the campaign.
No.
But what about the IVF? The injection is in three days.
Don't worry.
Honey…
I can't just let everyone down like that.
Honey!
And if I say no?
Well, that's serving the extreme right.
And the IVF? Don't worry. I got this.
Hmm…
Mandela and Winnie?
Better. Amadou &amp; Mariam.
We can't see, but we walk together.
Because they're blind, so, you know…
Yeah, I know who Amadou &amp; Mariam are.
You're always doing that!
Goodness! Just stop!
Are you Malian? No.
Knock it off then. It's not even funny. Yeah, sorry.
Stop making fun of them all the time. You're done. It's like, whoa.
Sorry.
You scared me. Stop it.
Okay, love you. Yeah.
Hey.
Are we back in the game or what?
Quitting was a mistake, but I'm here now, and I'm excited.
Any news on William?
He hasn't been responding. He's gone.
We don't need him anyway right now. I'll be in charge of the campaign.
Okay.
And where are we at in the polls today?
Low. Really low. Tied with Corinne the Green.
Okay. We can't do any worse than that. We've got a few days left. Let's hustle.
What? Of course I sent out my résumé.
No one's responding…
Guys, the reason I came back is also this little bastard here.
Now that he's here, let's get to work.
Okay. There's lots of work for us to do.
That's right. Tonight, 5:00 p.m., Stéphane Blé on Instagram.
We need all our contacts on every social media platform.
Why Stéphane Blé? Because he's the Hello. Stéphane Blé.
Thank you very much. April 10th. Stéphane Blé.
Vote for Blé.  We reach out to people.
We need to reach wide. Stéphane Blé.
We reach out to the voters on their own turf.
It's 60? Yeah.
And vote Blé.  We have a lot to say.
We need to be heard. Unheard of. Doin' free school lunches.
I know you guys are starvin'. You're starving.
Anyway, it's our last chance.
And before the end, I promise, we'll hit 'em hard, and they'll feel it.
Yeah.
The reason I'm ending my campaign right here…
is because, right here, we've got problems.
Hmm?
And also the solutions.
Ah.
I wanna love the police.
I wanna trust them and feel the police will protect us.
When I see the police here…
I hope I can run to our officers.
To embrace. Huh?
We need to trust each other.
We need to stop suspecting each other. Sorry.
Sorry. Excuse me. Sorry.
Uh… Yeah.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Sorry, sorry. It's because I wasn't feeling well.
But I'm better now and with you till the end. Sorry.
Go on. Go on.
You know…
…I'm not a big drinker, and recently, I overdid it.
Oh, no. I was pretty out of it for a sec.
Ooh.
While I was out of it, I saw things.
Some crazy things,
like my mom getting to sleep through the night,
without kids below her window
always listening to Niska or arguing the whole night.
While I was out of it, I saw sisters able to walk down the street, unafraid,
in leggings, or a hijab, and no one gave a crap.
A skirt, even. A skirt.
Short skirts with heels, or maybe boots
In my vision, young men and women walked with their heads high,
without worrying about ID checks or about getting turned down for a job
because they don't look right or don't live in the right area.
In my vision, my homeland, our France, live united, reconciled,
able to look in the mirror and tell her children,
all her children,
"Your home is here."
Liberty, equality, brotherhood.
And security!
Hmm?
Right. Security too. You're right.  Thank you.
Yeah, that sounds good. "Liberty, equality, security."
Yes!
Whoo!
Bravo!
Long live your vision!
I knew he wasn't more leftwing than me.
Because he's Black. That means nothing, "because he's Black."
I'm leftwing to the bone. So?
Is the prefecture deal mine or what? Who cares?
What's that mean, "who cares"?
Listen to me. To hell with the prefecture.
I'm worried about your cousin. You know what he's saying out there?
"Liberty, equality…"
And? "Security." Security!
All right? This moron's turning rightwing.
And nobody cares. He's taking eight percent from me.
He's stealing. So, we need to react.
Security, all right. I say Lamine.
What, Lamine?
The boy, Lamine. He works with him. So what?
Ah, well, "security" equals "Lamine."
Yeah, but he's a boy. Lamine's just feeling lost.
But he's not a thug. He's just a boy, yeah?
Yeah. He's still a delinquent.
We'll arrest the kid together.
Hey, totally. I don't even know. You can believe me or not, okay?
Okay, my buddy's here. Call you back. Lamine, my man!
What's up? How's it going? You good? What's up?
You, how's it going?
Lamine, there's about thirty thou here.
You mean Désiré wants to help our campaign?
Stéphane is family. You know that.
Of course we'll help.
Seriously, you don't trust us? No, just checkin', aye.
Hey, come on. What's all this? Hey.
Calm down. I don't want this.
Same as cash. You just need to sell it. I don't want it!
Are you serious? I don't want it!
Nobody move! Nobody move! I said don't move!
Don't move!  Stop right there!
Stop running!
Yeah, Marion? It's Lamine.
Yeah, I fucked myself here. I need help.
No, I can't be on France Info. I told you, man. I can't.
I'm at the clinic, waiting for Marion, for the IVF right now.
It's just not possible. It's happening today, man.
Yeah. See you, William. Bye.
Your wife still hasn't come? No, she's pretty late. I don't get it.
She's someone who's early. I'm just as confused.
At worst, uh,
can we maybe put the embryo in some kind of fridge?
Like, because it's an egg?
Twentyfour, fortyeight hours maybe, like…
Well Well, no.
You can't just… The process won't work that way.
It's now or never, at the moment.
Ah.
Hello? Where are you?  Stéph?
Come to the Boulevard Hotel. We've got a major problem.
Please, please, hurry. Hurry! Okay, I'm coming.
See you soon. Stay there, all right? Stay there.
So sorry. I have to go.  Oh.
Really, so sorry. Sorry.  That's all right.
Yes?
It's me.
You okay? What happened? No, no, I'm not okay. Oh, Stéphane.
See there's…
Those boys, Désiré, Lotfi, those guys tried to trick Lamine.
They say, "Yeah, we'll give you some money for the campaign,"
when it was actually pot.
Stéphane, I fought Lotfi.
It's just, I hit him. He took a bad fall. Bad.
That was when the police got there. They were waiting for us.
WILLIAM: TURN ON THE NEWS!!!
A bombshell has been dropped
squarely in the middle of the presidential election.
The hackers, probably from Russia,
reportedly had an accomplice inside one of the campaign teams
and exposed emails of the candidates.
On both the right and the left, many staff members are in a panic.
Any comments on the millions embezzled?
No, no, no. No comment, please. No comment, please.
Where do you think this was leaked from, Mr. Andréï?
Oh, this is crazy. Oh, this is insane.
Are you going to end your campaign?
We received an official press release just now,
with the campaign committee for Éric Andréï
attesting to the withdrawal of the candidate at this time.
I repeat…
Éric Andréï is no longer a candidate in the presidential election.
But the frontrunner in the polls is not the only victim of this recent data leak.
Another scandal has seemingly bombed the candidacy of Etienne Durandeau.
Mr. Durandeau…
Listen, I don't comment on foolish rumors.
The rightwing candidate is at great risk of accusations of high treason,
and his immediate withdrawal as a candidate
was also just recently announced.
The latest candidate to be affected by these leaks
and forced to rapidly terminate his campaign,
leader of the "blue boots" extreme right, Fred Cognard.
Mr. Cognard, can you  Get the hell back!
Were other animals involved? Hey! The dog consented!
The dog consented!
No complaints are currently filed against Cognard,
but there are several compromising videos seemingly showing Cognard with a dog
that have already gotten tens of millions of views online.
Only two of the main campaigns appear to be unaltered
by this embarrassing cataclysm.
That of Stéphane Blé, in complete disarray right now,
and that of Corrine Douanier,
who chose not to use emails in her campaign
in order to reduce her carbon footprint.
As the campaign is ending, Blé and Douanier may well be the opponents
in the second round of the swiftly approaching election.
Tonight, our guests will be analyzing this truly astonishing case in our his
Stéphane, you'll get to the second round. Turn myself in, it's over.
We'll make a choice…
for you to take off on the run.
Are you serious? Just until the second round.
You'll disappear to Normandy, where Nora's mother is.
Mo'll watch your back. I'll say Lamine got an internship.
You're resting for IVF. Let's do it.
Are you crazy? Just stop. We're not doing that.
Have you lost your mind? Go on the run?
But this It's crazy!
Turning ourselves in at least gives us a chance.
Otherwise, we're fleeing. They won't go easy on you then.
No. Wait, Stéphane. Stop this right now.
We are in the second round.  No. No!
If he turns himself in, I have to leave the campaign.
No. No, but Stéphane isn't doing this.
It's me. I decided. Let's go.
No, wait. I'm stuck now with no choice!
Lamine! There's no choice, Marion!
Hey, Stéphane, are you serious right now?
Yeah, Mo. Yeah, it's Lamine. Yeah, I'm with Marion now.
Listen, you need to pick us up right now. We're at the hotel behind the national.
No, are you stupid? Not the soccer team, the national highway.
Mo, it's an emergency!
It's 7:59 p.m.,
and the faces of the two candidates for the second vote
will be revealed to all.
Five, four…
…three, two, one.
Stéphane Blé and Corinne Douanier…
…will move on to the second round of the presidential election.
Stéphane Blé, local monitor until a few weeks ago
when his campaign launched…
You hear me? You're gonna win it! You'll win it!
…face off in the second round of the presidential election.
…in two weeks, it's a big moment,
as France will either have its first Black president in history,
or else, its very first female president.
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Screaming "One day…" ♪
♪ "One day…" ♪
♪ "…I'll be president" ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪