A NETFLIX SERIES
Hey, Tarik. Can you give me the keys, please?
Yeah, I'll get 'em for you. Thanks much, man.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
You, what do you do in… What do you mean by that?
No, it's a question. I'm not Am I asking what you do?
Hey, no, wait. I'm just kidding.
What? Lamine.
I'm taking the campaign digital. Ah.
He's the one sending out a tweet tomorrow about the State Thugs.
Totally. Do I think it's good?
I'd say that the music video's junk, no real production budget.
But the song is real. Yeah.
"Marianne, you bitch." No.
It talked about how It didn't do anything good.
Just drop it now.
Let's concentrate on the team. Oh, yeah, the team.
I got someone great. There's Mo, there. He's my cuz.
He'll be in charge of my security. And he, uh, has experience in security?
Yeah. He's listening.
I watched over Stéphane since we were boys.
He couldn't protect himself. Whoa.
In fifth grade, I kept fighting your bullies for you.
I was in first grade. Come on.
Yeah. That's actually good.
Security really isn't very complex.
Just figure out which guys can't be trusted,
and that's easy to do.
Yeah. I can tell who's after Stéphane.
The Freemasons.
What? Yeah. The state.
Israel, that's obvious.  Whoa.
What "whoa"? Whoa what? Whoa, whoa. Hey, hey.
I'm speaking the truth. Well…
Calm down, man.  You can't say anything anymore.
We need to stop this, or he'll pull a real Benalla on us.
Okay, I found the keys.  Ah, okay. Let's go.
Bro, calm down. We're good.
Voilà. There.
Just be careful of the asbestos.
Huh? Uh, about the rats, chill.
Clean up any trash and it'll be fine.
So, enjoy.
Welcome.  Why are you showing us this?
A storage place, or what? It's our HQ.
It Our HQ, really? Yeah.
Listen, we have a few weeks to get 500 mayors to support us.
We have to work from somewhere, right?
I'll be working from my place.
Thank you.
Bravo! Bravo!
Listen, I did what you asked. I started my security firm.
Good. I have guys ready to make some money.
But, uh, thing is, we're waiting for you. I mean… You know?
Hey, remember who wrote your regulations?
Remember who got you bankers? What can I give you now?
As the mayor? Nothing, peanuts.
Now, if I were the president…
That's just a whole other scale, but I…
I need to get elected.
But some folks still keep on getting in my way.
Like who? Your cousin.
Oh. He isn't really much help.
He's perturbing, see, because he splits up the left.
And if he campaigns, I'm ruined. He'll split up our votes. You understand?
So you wanna see if I can Sh!
No, I'm not saying "want." I just ww….
What means are you…
I suggest he drops out?
Uh. Yes, that way, we… Ah.
Everyone can go ahead with their respective projects.
Hey, what? I touched your beard.
Apologies. Watch it.
No, I touched No. Don't do that.
Lamine! Yeah.
I know. That's what I keep telling you, man.
Lamine! Yeah, I'm on the phone here!
Hey. Poster. Huh?
We good?  What's this?
Yeah, there. Like that.
Mmhmm.
Purple? Color of the Vatican, seriously?
Hmm?
The Pope. The Church.
Slavery and colonization. Are you serious, dude?
ItItIt's the Lakers too. Yeah, and kids too.
The Lakers' kids? No, just for kids.
Hello. Oh! Hey!
How are you, Yasmine? I'm great.
Hey, listen, uh, Stéphane.
Let me introduce you to Yasmine. Hey. Great.
She's going to take care of our campaign and strategy.
She's a genius. She studied politics.
Is that right? ENA. Top school. Wow.
Great. Nice to meet you. Yeah, well, I'm super happy to be here.
I've been waiting for a candidacy like yours for a long time.
Yeah. Committed, socialist, radical.
We'll beat everyone with our hard work. Well, yeah, cool.
Yeah. Super happy. I saw you looking a bit lost.
Let me introduce Didier. He's my Didi, my Did.
The giant D. Oh, we caused a lot of trouble.
Stéphane Blé. Hey there.
It'll be nice to meet people, see new faces, chitchat.
Since leaving the clinic, you know, I've been a little
Hang on, what clinic? Because my wife
Hey. Oh, you scoundrel.
This guy here is getting us our sponsors. He knows everyone. He's a monster.
There are 42,000 representatives, and he knows 40,000.
Oh, yeah?  Yeah.
Importantly, I know what they like. Yeah.
For example, the mayor of Saint Goulinard, he likes Calvados.
Saint Goulinard. He knows him.
And then, GeoffrononOise, he just gobbles headcheese.
Ah!  The one from PaurylesVignes…
Yeah? He likes little Thai chicks.
Eighteen, nineteen.
Well, that's the legal age, so Yes, yes.
But we traveled to Pattaya together.
We won't keep you here.  Right.
Short on time and zero sponsors, so let's get moving. Uh, where's the
Here's the list
of who you'll go and visit.
Okay? Yeah, it's all there.
We're… We're rightwing? Yeah, rightwing.
I'm super excited, so ready to start work with you.
My pleasure. Impressive that the ENA has…
Has? Has…
Has what?
Alumni, yeah.
Okay. Yeah. Excuse me.
I didn't say anything before about Didier, but he needs work.
We have a zerotolerance policy on sexism.
Next time, I'm reporting it.  Oh, I agree.
So, uh, Yasmine,
here are the big, important ideas that we're going to defend, right here.
We worked hard on these. So, here they are.
We got free cafeterias, more social diversity,
universal income, more bonding between generations.
Listen, my goal is to win this.
Yeah, well, me too. All right? Strong measures first.
Mashallah. Identifiable. Let's examine Douanier.
The Green candidate.  Yeah.
Her zerowaste policy's intense. Each kilo's taxed a hundred euros.
Yeah, crazy.  It's great.
Just impossible to implement.
So, we will find a measure that can punch, that slaps.
Radical, disruptive. Uhhuh. Yeah. Mashallah. Disruptive.
Totally. So, it's super great to talk with you.
Uh, with us. Mashallah, mashallah.
It would be even better… Mashallah.
Seriously. Stop saying mashallah.
You say it a lot.  Please.
Alhamdulillah.
Honestly, without strong measures,
we won't get sponsors, and the campaign's over.
Wait, wait. Easy.
No, just eas Please, go easy. Don't thrust. Don't get crazy.
I'm gonna jab it into the fat. There's more than enough here.
A better living wage is strong, so that's my plan now.
Uh, and, you've got those funds?
Gonna sell the Eiffel Tower? No.
No, seriously, you need to strike at the real problems.
For an example…
zero social charges on takehome pay.
Boom. Simple, effective. People will get it.
No, no!
Zerointerest loans for all entrepreneurs.
See? Like that.
Come up with leftwing measures, since I'm left, at the core.
All right, fine. Go and gimme the shot. I need to rest.
Do it. Go ahead. But I did. I'm serious.
No. No way.  I did.
Wow.
Yes, I saw them both one night. He brought her to Maki's.
You know, that kind of of African restaurant.
Yes, he took her there to have fish.  Jeannette!
I left the groceries on the third floor and some in the car.
Bring those here, Stéphane.
That bastard! He ruined me!
He emptied my entire bank account!
Just talk to her.
I'llI'll talk to her, yeah. I won't be treated this way.
Then go ahead, Stéphane. You have to do something.
Hey, Jeannette, come on. It's polite to say "hello."
Hello, Stéphane.
Hi, Auntie. Hi, handsome.
Mom, we need to talk about Jeannette. I'm not in your campaign?
No.
Oh, this is it! Yes. It's media monitoring.
There. That's where you'll focus, Simone.
So this, um… Yes.
You'll take a notebook, like this, your tools.
There's a TV in there. Watch every single channel.
When someone says "Stéphane," bam, you write it.
Yeah. That's it, love. Okay?
Uhhuh. All right, Simone. Welcome on board.
Uh, guys, I talked to Didier.  How's it going?
He's struggling.
Right now, what he needs
is a strong argument to convince the mayors.
So we need some real focus.
We need the measure that lets you stand out from the others.
Now, you're a nice guy who's Black and raps pretty badly…
but evokes the block, you know, in some ways.
But the bad block.
The block that's dirty, the block that's disgusting,
the block with riots, the block that's violent, uh…
Gangs, Kalashnikovs, uh, abandoned babies.
Uh, fridges that tumble off thethe rooftops on firemen
who are saving people, what's more.
Hey, William. The hijab. Sorry, what?
That's plenty.
We need a measure. There you are.
Oh, you've settled in nicely.
Pfft… Why's he here, dude?
Why d'you hang around with this clown? He's family.
He's family? I'm not family?  Yeah. Right.
Yeah, you are. Aren't I family? Let's chat. Come on.
Go on, Stéphane. We're good.
I'll contact the polling institute to adjust your placement.
Look, it's funny, your little stunt, but you know it's pointless, right?
No, I wouldn't say that.
Would you say that a Black president can win this?
Hey, this is France, dude.
If you were a manager at McDonald's, huge. What's this?
The point's not to be the president. Feel me? It's about our message.
Oh.
Hey, dreams are great, but just look. There's no room for that here.
Really? The president? You're losing it now, for real.
Forget it. It's not for you. Why do you care?
Tell me, what's your problem? It's not about me.
But you're causing issues. You know, it's politics. It's dogeatdog.
You think your guys gave a shit till you made it on TV?
You don't matter to those fools.
Me, I care about you. You care about me?
Of course.
Well, vote for me then in April. Excuse me. I've gotta work.
Wallah. I'm gonna get those sponsors.
These are people who aren't afraid to get up in the morning and…
and get started working.
Yes?
Well, now, a lovely owner. Morning, ma'am.
How may I help?
How could you help me more than you already are
with this splendid store?
The enchanting salon
that has such a wealth of life, such community and ethnic interactivity.
And your braids are so beautiful.
Can you take them away?
We're gonna take a break. Let's step back.
Let me stop you there.
It's obvious why you're here,
but I'm not part of the campaign with Stéphane.
Your husband, Stéphane, is bound for a bright future, but…
to get it, he needs to pick a side, like my side.
We really need to block the right wing, chiefly the extreme right.
Because, you'll agree with me,
it's at our front door.
Hmm?
Tell me about your loan forfor the salon? How's that?
Are you getting by? Making it work? You know about that?
It's my city. I just keep track.
Let me assist. I know people who do great work at the bank.
And, in fact,
I believe this lady is eligible for a municipalfunded loan support.
The municipal aid fund. Mmhmm.
For entrepreneurs and bolstering diversity. Yeah.
That exists here? It does now, yes.
Let me give you my card. Call anytime.
I'll count on you.
Talk to him.
We need him, but on our own team.
Right.
I won't be voting for that guy. Look at his face.
Mr. Andréï.
No. That's not a reason.
Don't vote for a face. Vote for ideas, all right?
Now focus.
Yes, often. But that's enough.
No, go ahead.
Just tell me, uh, what comes into your minds.
And please, answer honestly.
Well, it's a Black, uh, guy?
Mmhmm.
One who has a disability.
Yeah, the, um, "Solutions come from below,"
his legs were amputated, I bet.
Oh, a paraplegic. Yeah.
That's awful.  No, no.
No, disability is, uh, missing the point.
Uh, Stéphane here is running for president.
And this study will help us understand how people see him.
But isn't that the guy with the disgusting video
where he insults Marianne, like, uh, says all that…
He's… He's a piece of shit, that guy. Yeah.
Well, let's go ahead. I'll say some words.
And you raise your hand and tell me if they mean something to you.
Okay. Confidence?
Security?
Well, "Black."
Mm.  Mmhmm.
Uh, "dealer."  Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Um, uh, poverty.  Oh, yes.
Mmhmm.
Polygamy.
Yeah, that too.  I agree.
Uh, guys, it's a long shot.
Your path is a very, very, very long one. Why say "a long way"? How much longer?
We can catch up. I've never seen such bad results.
Guy Georges as president has better chances than Stéphane.
Whoa.
Wow. The writer?
No, that's George Sand. I mean…
Guy Georges? Oh, shit!
Guy Georges, the rapist? Yeah, the rapist. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, we're very We're so beyond anything.
Wow. Okay.
What's after that, Hitler? Sorry, I need to take this.
What could be worse?
Yes, Etienne?  How did the study go?
Your guy's doing all right? Listen, he's been doing great.
No, really. The clip is, uh, completely behind us.
It's done.
So now, moving on, the priority is what?
The sponsorships.  Okay.
You absolutely need to bring me all those signatures, okay?
I'll see what I can do. Otherwise, game over, finished.
It can't be really possible that I'm rating lower than Guy Georges.
He never ran for president, right?
No, I'm being serious. HisHis image is, uh… Pfft.
The sympathy he elicits is… It's crazy.
I'm making it work anyway.
You see, we just need to figure out this measure.
Damn it.
The right to vote at 15?
You're grasping now.
What's the matter?
You want Peppa Pig?
Here.
Your daughter? No, she's my niece.
But can you explain something to me? Peppa Pig is allowed?
Isn't pork haram?
And Peppa's a pig and all.
No, I'm really asking you.
Well, Didier needs info on you to reassure the mayors,
and the media will start digging soon, so let's explore your past, okay?
All right. If there's a stain, we'll find it.
No. I'm a hundred percent clean. Relax.
Yeah? My past is clean. Oh, yeah.
All right. So, fire away, huh?
Okay, great. Any financial fraud?
I get my tax exempted.
Okay. We're good on the criminal record. Have you cheated on Ms. Marion?
Are you mental?
Hey, a hijab doesn't mean I don't know about things.
If there's anything, come clean to me. That's not me at all, man.
I have never cheated on Marion.
No way.
Okay, so you're clean regarding the MeToo movement?
A hundred percent clean.
So, yeah, keep on going. Okay.
Not even some groping, some unwanted flirting?
Dick pic? No way.
Okay? Okay, okay. Not bad.
"Not bad." It's normal.
Oh!
Yeah.
Six or seven years ago, before I met Marion, maybe.
I guess, I could've, uh…
convinced a woman a little bit, not much, during a shindig.
Nothing too… serious.
Convinced how? Ah!
You know, right?
We were there drinking. We were wasted. You know?
I mean, she didn't tell me, like, "no,"
but I'm not sure she specifically said "yes."
Oh, man. That's ancient! You know? Life, right?
What happened exactly? Tell me.
I'm warning you, I'm not working for a rapist.
No. Please, wait, Yasmine. Calm down.
We need more data. You need to remember the girl.
Calm down. Her name's not coming to me, man.
You had sex and didn't even bother to remember her name, dude?
Yo, I got a question, real quick.
Uh, is it the candidate who needs to stay clean?
Or like the whole entire team? Because
The whole team. Oh, no. Please, no. Keep quiet.
Listen, when was it? And where?
You need to find me a name, an address. Anything. We need to find her.
Because you realize that if not, we stop here.
No presidential election, no campaign, nothing.
You'll end up in prison, rotting, for assault.
Stop it, Yasmine. Can you stop?  We need to face reality.
But we don't know for sure.
Please, Stéphane, you need to focus. Think hard. Where can we find this girl?
I'm the same.
'Cause my old girl went off talking shit to everyone because she left for months
and I had a thing with a member of her family, her cousin.
She was crazy. A memory. Think about it, hard.
A street, a youth club.
Come on.  A first name.
I know.
What are we doing? Stop.
I knew he was weird from his face. What face?
Judging a candidate What face?
I'm not judging Worse than a voter.
You can tell he's weird  Just be positive.
If we start off thinking we're losing
You think the mayors are gonna sponsor a rapist?
Oh, great job. Presumption of innocence is over.
Whoa. So what's this?
Well, I remember she was a volunteer here.
Oh, man. You're the presidential runner.
Yeah, that's me. Yeah, I recognize you.
It's cool you came to the fair.
And we're trying to raise money for a ski trip.
Oh, that's great.
Come in. Ya'll are welcome.
All right, my little president.  So where's this girl?
She's there. Her, there?
Yeah, in the pink. Okay, come.
No.  Come on!
Hello. Hi. Uh, yes?
See that? What?
She doesn't remember me. Wait, no. Go on. Go.
Go on. Go ahead. Go, go.
Do you remember, like six years ago, the party for Métalisé?
I'm sorry? Apparently, there's history with you two.
It's not much. You might not have even noticed.
You know, it's possible it didn't occur.  Hmm.
Try smiling. Maybe that's it.
We met at Métalisé's birthday party,
and, uh, after, we went back to mine, and we screwed, I think.
So we wanna know if it was, like, uh….
If it was consensual, you mean. Not "screwed" but "made love."
Right, consensual.  It had to be, I think, right?
Wow! My God!
You're still alive. Why are you here?
Well… actually, we were looking for you.
Oh, my God.
It's all a blank? Well
What did he do? It's
You don't remember what happened that night?
No, he doesn't remember. He, uh… So, what did… Why?
Is it wrong? Nothing happened.
Nothing?
Not a thing. Not a thing?
Nothing. Nada. Nothing means nothing.
But wait, something went down. No, no.
What happened is, we went back to yours because you were smashed.
Afterward, you proposed we start banging. Okay. He requested.
Hey, but I said no right away. She said no.
You wanted to know if it was your teeth.
I said yes. You started crying. Ha.
You fell asleep. I left right away. Ah.
Done.  Done. That means it's nothing.
It was nothing, no rape.  Nothing.
I meant, no contact. You what?
No, nothing happened. This is great. He just cried.
My apologies. Vote for Blé on April 10th. We're off now. Have a great night, day.
Let's go. You sure we didn't bang?
We're certain.
It's fine. He's clean. We can start with the interviews.
Wait, wait. Don't go yet.
You wanna dance? No, no.
Come on. Uh, yes. Well, of course he does.
I mean, he's a killer dancer. No.
As a new presidential candidate, you have to dance
No, I don't want to.  Go, go.
Come on. ♪ She ready, she ready ♪
Yeah. Uh. Uh. Let's dance.
Ay!
What? What?
Hey! Woohoo!
Oh!
That's hood.
♪ Dee, dididee, dididee, dididay! ♪
That's a bad sign.
This is not good. Not good.
Hey, hey, hey! Where are you going with that?
Look, Issa got all these drinks and snacks for us.
She bought organic too. Hmm. This is all organic?
He got this with coupons?
That's actually our main measure.
"Making meals… for a steal."
Wait, wait. Are we stealing meals now, man?
No, no, no.
Making meals for a steal. Like free meals.
Nothin' is free. Everybody's a customer or a product.
You doin' this on purpose? This is France, okay?
And we can vote.  Yeah.
We have freedom of movement. Okay? And we also have freedom of speech.
Freedom of speech, freedom of expression.
Just not about the Jewish. Whoa, whoa. No, no, stop there.
Okay.
What I'd like is good nutrition for people here, okay?
Imagine, grabbing a cart, going to the grocery store,
and getting whatever you like.
All organic food that uses supply chains that are short, uh, local.
Then you don't have to pay a thing.  Good Lord.
That's stealing!  No, Mom.
It's a revolution. Uh, Stéph?
Now, you and I know that I'm bad at math,
but this revolution is gonna cost us billions.
I mean, if every French person goes into a supermarket
to buy organic produce and they don't pay,
uhuh, how do we make it work for about 67 million people?
He's right.
This is absurd. It's nuts. It's completely impossible.
Well, listen, I just ran the numbers, and it's costly,
but in ten years, health care savings will pay for it.
Wow. In 30 seconds, you did all that? That's right.
Wow, okay.  Hold on.
It must be. I don't We're gonna save much more than that.
Picture my idea.
If your meals are better, your mind is stronger,
you study better, you mess up less.
So there are fewer cops, fewer judges.
We get these meals in fridges and we empty the prisons, guys.
That's great.  Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! All right. Okay. I mean, my
No, I had this exact idea two years ago. Yeah, same one.
So basically, the measure then is, "Making meals… for a steal."
Amen!  It sounds great.
I had the same slogan. Crazy.
Make it "halal for a steal."
And now…
…you get the Arabs.
Trust me, they're bunches. Too many. But that's another debate. That's, uh…
Per square kilometer, you've got, uh…
The mayors loved it.  Yeah?
We're taking off like crazy. We've got loads of sponsors.
It's gonna be a long road, but, man, this idea is awesome.
Mm. What? Wait.
Oh, hey, you know, Andréï came by just the other day.
The salon.
What did he want? To be helpful. To help me out.
Shit.  Stéphane.
He can help me with the loan.
It could be such a weight off of us, a breath of fresh air.
Especially with our, uh…
We know you're not gonna be president.
I mean, Andréï, he will be the president.
Work with Andréï on his stuff.
Just give him a couple of measures that you think matter a lot.
It's a really, really awesome thing. So he waltzed in and turned you.
Is that it? He didn't.
He'll pay back your business loan for you, and that's it.
Forget Négritude, Frantz Fanon What did you say? What was that?
You're a great example of all the problems we have in Africa.
Oh, all right. Okay.
Someone shows up, flashes some cash, and there you go, all the sellouts start
What? Wait, what? Me?
Me? I'm a sellout? It seems so. Maybe, yeah.
You're pretty content when this sellout works to pay the bills around here, right?
And you're sitting there, "I'm gonna be president."
A shiny dome with nothing in it! What can you do, except judge people?
"I'm gonna be president." "I'm president." It's nonsense!
You know what you are? Another Bokassa!
What about you, Mobutu?
With that nasty face of yours! Giscard d'Estaing!
I completely understand, Marion. No, no, I respect his decision.
It's one of the virtues of plurality, I believe.
Yes.
Yes. Yes?
Uh, pardon me, your…
Oh, your business loan! Of course. I'm here to help you.
I myself will handle your case. You may count on me.
All right. All right, all right. Goodbye then. You too. Bye now.
You, miss, can put your loan up your ass.
Thanks. Let's take a break.
Jérôme!  Yes, what?
Excuse me.
You mind grabbing me some coffee, please?
We're in deep shit. Why?
Because that other idiot is campaigning. Apparently his wife couldn't convince him.
Don't panic. The campaign is still ongoing.
Not much longer. How is he with sponsors now?
Well, I've put pressure on them to dismiss him,
but I suspect the right's been helping.
It's obvious the right is helping him out.
He's not stealing their votes. He's stealing votes from me!
I mean, last week, we were at 23. Now, it's 22.
The barrier for the second round is 18. Eighteen.
We must act. There's nothing to do.
We must act quickly. You're the frontrunner.
The top dog, number one.
Blé won't last. You know that. You just need to concentrate.
You'll get to the Elysée. You're almost there. Stay focused.
Okay? Mm… no.
Come here, Jérôme.
You occasionally have good advice, but you're still a bit green.
Strike a sharp blow soon, like that.
What? I mean, play dirty.
No, Éric.
Now, I'm not expecting you to behave like a thug.
See, me and you wouldn't behave like thugs.
Regrettably,
I manage a city with plenty of thugs.
Plenty.
Wonderful! Thank you.
This sponsorship means a lot. Thank you so much, Mrs. Mayor.
Or is it Mrs. Mayoress? I always forget.
We accept the sponsorship with great pleasure.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Uh, Didier is en route.
He's got our final sponsorship.
Yes!
We're now three hours away…
Yo! …from the deadline.
So we're pretty set.
Yes! Yes! Yes! No way, dude.
Hey, Stéphane, you did it! I told you, didn't I?
You gotta dream big. I dreamed big.
We dreamed big. That's how it goes. Exactly, man.
Congratulations. Good work today. This is crazy. This is crazy. It's crazy!
Didier? So? What?
Sorry, guys. I called in every favor. I tried everything.
I, uh, thought for sure the last one was set.
I even offered to pleasure her.  Huh?
No, just kidding. I think I did it. I don't know.
Anyway, what we know for sure is…
the sponsorship's gone.
Fuck.  I don't believe it.
I can't believe it. This is not happening!
We can't stop at 499. C'mon people.  What a coincidence.
What a complete coincidence, one missing.
That's clearly a plot from the
Can you just cut it out, all right?  Stéphane, what now?
You really needed 500 signatures in order to run?
If we don't have those, we're done.
What if we do a robbery?  Mo, please, seriously, man.
We're not kidding around.  I just think that if
Man, stop talking nonsense!
WHAT FUTURE FOR OUR PLANET?
Behave yourself.  We have no business here.
Let's bounce.  We do.
She's a tree hugger. She likes Black people.
And she hasn't given out her sponsorship yet.
Good evening, sir.
I'd like to know if
And what makes you think I'm a man?
Well, good evening, ma'am.
I would just like to know Ah, okay.
According to you, one's a man or a woman? I don't know.
I mean, there are some certain elements that indicate that you are clearly a man.
You have a beard, for one thing. Oh, yes, all men have beards.
And women wear skirts. Hmm.
In most cases, yes, that's how it tends to happen.
Although there are bearded women. Come on, William, stop it. Excuse me.
Where is Corinne Douanier, please?
Over there. Thanks.
What the hell are we doing here? What?
It's Madagascar in here. You saw that guy. I don't know. Look at their faces.
Tall people, skinny people, weird Calm down, calm down.
John Lennon. Excuse me?
Sinéad O'Connor there. Ah, greetings.
Hello. Take this.
No, let me handle this, please.
Let me do it.
Keep booking things. I'm in topnotch form.
Yes? Hello.
Hi, it's Stéphane Blé, a candidate for president.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Uh, William Crozon, campaign manager, éminence grise.
The architect of all this. Aidedecamp, or chief of staff, if you
I know what an aidedecamp is.
Why are you explaining? Because I'm a woman?
No, it's No, I'm like you, in politics.
Being a woman, no problem. I went to school.
It's crazy. You speak, uh… That was Chinese, right?
Why? Because I recognized it.
You were in China and everything for…
Yeah. IsIs it
Could we possibly talk outside for a few minutes?
Yeah, I was just about to do rounds.
Join me. Cool.
Without this nohoper, though. I'm sorry.
Wow. So that's a blunt attack there.
Sorry, a "nohoper"? Please, that's… Oh.
My greatest passion is politics. Hello. Calm down.
Yeah, super, me too. I'm into politics.
Not men in suits. Love it.
No, they cut us off from our base, thanks.
I'll be passing on that. Shall we? Yes, let's go.
I'm not in a suit. It's a cardigan. Okay.
Mismatched, with wornout shoes. Good evening.
Oh.
It's crazy what gets thrown out.
So you're a mayor and a candidate. Could you give your sponsorship to me?
It'll depend on what your politics are.
Normally, I'm left. But with the mess they made, I'm not sure.
Oh, but "neither left nor right" generally means right wing.
No, but I'm not.
I know I won't be elected, okay?
I wanna talk about things we don't hear about.
Like talk about associations that don't get funding
and about folks struggling in the projects.
My life.
Thoughts on nuclear power are?
Nuclear power, I don't give a fuck.
Come on, no.
Listen, there are kids going to school with empty stomachs.
And some of them only eat once per day at school.
That can't be possible here. We can't allow it.
And folks need to hear about it. They need to know.
Want it?
Do you like green?
Yeah.
Please, take.
It's not from a…
And so, we have 500 sponsors!
My man!
To Stéph!  All right, man!
We made it!
I never could have done it, man. Wow. No way I could've.
It's thanks to you, my brother.
Hi. Thanks.
Cheers, man. This is good. Good. Mmhmm.
Thanks a lot. You made it work. Yeah, of course.
Ah, yeah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!  Ah, yeah! Yes!
All right.
♪ Amen, hallelujah, amen, hallelujah ♪
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Get back! Get back!
Look out! Let me at these bastards!
Look out!
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screamin' "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪
♪ Screaming "One day…" ♪
♪ "One day…" ♪
♪ "…I'll be president" ♪
♪ Maneuver, sliding through the mess ♪
♪ Screaming "One day, I'll be president" ♪